{
  "javascript_array_methods": {
    "level": [
      {
        "one": [
          {
            "position": 0,
            "question": "This method joins arrays and returns an array with the joined arrays",
            "answer": "concat"
          },
          {
            "position": 1,
            "question": "This method checks whether an object is an array",
            "answer": "isArray"
          },
          {
            "position": 2,
            "question": "This property sets or returns the number of elements in an array",
            "answer": "length"
          },
          {
            "position": 3,
            "question": "This method joins all elements of an array into a string",
            "answer": "join"
          },
          {
            "position": 4,
            "question": "This method removes the last element of an array, and returns that element",
            "answer": "pop"
          },
          {
            "position": 5,
            "question": "This method adds new elements to the end of an array, and returns the new length",
            "answer": "push"
          },
          {
            "position": 6,
            "question": "This method reverses the order of the elements in an array",
            "answer": "reverse"
          },
          {
            "position": 7,
            "question": "This method sorts the elements of an array",
            "answer": "sort"
          },
          {
            "position": 8,
            "question": "This method converts an array to a string, and returns the result",
            "answer": "toString"
          }
        ]
      },

      {
        "two": [
          {
            "position": 0,
            "question": "This method checks if every element in an array pass a test",
            "answer": "every"
          },
          {
            "position": 1,
            "question": "This method creates a new array with every element in an array that pass a test",
            "answer": "filter"
          },
          {
            "position": 2,
            "question": "This method check if an array contains the specified element",
            "answer": "includes"
          },
          {
            "position": 3,
            "question": "This method calls a function for each array element",
            "answer": "forEach"
          },
          {
            "position": 4,
            "question": "This method searches the array for an element and returns its position",
            "answer": "indexOf"
          },
          {
            "position": 5,
            "question": "This method creates a new array with the result of calling a function for each array element",
            "answer": "map"
          },
          {
            "position": 6,
            "question": "This method removes the first element of an array, and returns that element",
            "answer": "shift"
          },
          {
            "position": 7,
            "question": "This method selects a part of an array, and returns the new array",
            "answer": "slice"
          }
        ]
      },

      {
        "three": [
          {
            "position": 0,
            "question": "This method returns the primitive value of an array",
            "answer": "valueOf"
          },
          {
            "position": 1,
            "question": "This method adds new elements to the beginning of an array, and returns the new length",
            "answer": "unshift"
          },
          {
            "position": 2,
            "question": "This method adds/removes elements from an array",
            "answer": "splice"
          },
          {
            "position": 3,
            "question": "This method checks if any of the elements in an array pass a test",
            "answer": "some"
          },
          {
            "position": 4,
            "question": "This method returns the index of the first element in an array that pass a test",
            "answer": "findIndex"
          },
          {
            "position": 5,
            "question": "This method returns the value of the first element in an array that pass a test",
            "answer": "find"
          },
          {
            "position": 6,
            "question": "This method fills the elements in an array with a static value",
            "answer": "fill"
          }
        ]
      },

      {
        "four": [
          {
            "position": 0,
            "question": "This method reduce the values of an array to a single value (going right-to-left)",
            "answer": "reduceRight"
          },
          {
            "position": 1,
            "question": "This method reduce the values of an array to a single value (going left-to-right)",
            "answer": "reduce"
          },
          {
            "position": 2,
            "question": "This method creates an array from an object",
            "answer": "from"
          },
          {
            "position": 3,
            "question": "This method copies array elements within the array, to and from specified positions",
            "answer": "copyWithin"
          },
          {
            "position": 4,
            "question": "This property returns the function that created the Array object's prototype",
            "answer": "constructor"
          }
        ]
      },

      {
        "five": [
          {
            "position": 0,
            "question": "This method returns a key/value pair Array Iteration Object",
            "answer": "entries"
          },
          {
            "position": 1,
            "question": "This property allows you to add properties and methods to an Array object",
            "answer": "prototype"
          },
          {
            "position": 2,
            "question": "This method returns a Array Iteration Object, containing the keys of the original array",
            "answer": "keys"
          },
          {
            "position": 3,
            "question": "This method searches the array for an element, starting at the end, and returns its position",
            "answer": "lastIndexOf"
          }
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  "http_request_methods": {
    "level": [
      {
        "one": [
          {
            "position": 0,
            "question": "The -BLANK- method requests a representation of the specified resource. Requests using -BLANK- should only retrieve data.",
            "answer": "GET"
          },
          {
            "position": 1,
            "question": "The -BLANK- method deletes the specified resource.",
            "answer": "DELETE"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "two": [
          {
            "position": 0,
            "question": "The -BLANK- method submits an entity to the specified resource, often causing a change in state or side effects on the server.",
            "answer": "POST"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "three": [
          {
            "position": 0,
            "question": "The -BLANK- method replaces all current representations of the target resource with the request payload.",
            "answer": "PUT"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "four": [
          {
            "position": 0,
            "question": "The -BLANK- method asks for a response identical to a GET request, but without the response body.",
            "answer": "HEAD"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "five": [
          {
            "position": 0,
            "question": "The -BLANK- method applies partial modifications to a resource.",
            "answer": "PATCH"
          },
          {
            "position": 1,
            "question": "The -BLANK- method performs a message loop-back test along the path to the target resource.",
            "answer": "TRACE"
          },
          {
            "position": 2,
            "question": "The -BLANK- method describes the communication options for the target resource.",
            "answer": "OPTIONS"
          },
          {
            "position": 3,
            "question": "The -BLANK- method establishes a tunnel to the server identified by the target resource.",
            "answer": "CONNECT"
          }
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  "javascript_error_types": {
    "level": [
      {
        "one": [
          {
            "position": 0,
            "question": "an error when trying to interpret syntactically invalid code",
            "answer": "SyntaxError"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "two": [
          {
            "position": 0,
            "question": "thrown when trying to pass a value as an argument to a function that does not allow a range that includes the value",
            "answer": "RangeError"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "three": [
          {
            "position": 0,
            "question": "an error when an operation could not be performed, typically (but not exclusively) when a value is not of the expected type",
            "answer": "TypeError"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "four": [
          {
            "position": 0,
            "question": "an error when trying to intan error when a variable that doesn't exist (or hasn't yet been initialized) in the current scope is referenced",
            "answer": "ReferenceError"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "five": [
          {
            "position": 0,
            "question": "represents an error when a global URI handling function was used in a wrong way",
            "answer": "URIError"
          }
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  "pg_promise_query_methods": {
    "level": [
      {
        "one": [
          {
            "position": 0,
            "question": "This query method expects one row or errors out. This query method is db.BLANK()",
            "answer": "one"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "two": [
          {
            "position": 0,
            "question": "This query method expects no rows or results, to be resolved with null. This query method is db.BLANK()",
            "answer": "none"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "three": [
          {
            "position": 0,
            "question": "This query method expects one or more rows. This query method is db.BLANK()",
            "answer": "many"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "four": [
          {
            "position": 0,
            "question": "This query method has no expectations. This query method is db.BLANK()",
            "answer": "any"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "five": [
          {
            "position": 0,
            "question": "This query method returns the raw results, useful for insert, update, and deletes. This query method is db.BLANK()",
            "answer": "result"
          }
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  "server_error_http_status_codes": {
    "level": [
      {
        "one": [
          {
            "position": 0,
            "question": "Internal Server Error",
            "answer": "500"
          },
          {
            "position": 1,
            "question": "Bad Gateway",
            "answer": "502"
          },
          {
            "position": 2,
            "question": "Network Authentication Required",
            "answer": "511"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "two": [
          {
            "position": 0,
            "question": "Service Unavailable",
            "answer": "503"
          },
          {
            "position": 1,
            "question": "Gateway Timeout",
            "answer": "504"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "three": [
          {
            "position": 0,
            "question": "Not Implemented",
            "answer": "501"
          },
          {
            "position": 1,
            "question": "HTTP Version Not Supported",
            "answer": "505"
          },
          {
            "position": 2,
            "question": "Network Connect Timeout Error",
            "answer": "599"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "four": [
          {
            "position": 0,
            "question": "Insufficient Storage",
            "answer": "507"
          },
          {
            "position": 1,
            "question": "Loop Detected",
            "answer": "508"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "five": [
          {
            "position": 0,
            "question": "Variant Also Negotiates",
            "answer": "506"
          },
          {
            "position": 1,
            "question": "Not Extended",
            "answer": "510"
          }
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  "client_error_http_status_codes": {
    "level": [
      {
        "one": [
          {
            "position": 0,
            "question": "Bad Request",
            "answer": "400"
          },
          {
            "position": 1,
            "question": "Unauthorized",
            "answer": "401"
          },
          {
            "position": 2,
            "question": "Not Found",
            "answer": "404"
          },
          {
            "position": 3,
            "question": "Forbidden",
            "answer": "403"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "two": [
          {
            "position": 0,
            "question": "Unsupported Media Type ",
            "answer": "415"
          },
          {
            "position": 1,
            "question": "Conflict",
            "answer": "409"
          },
          {
            "position": 2,
            "question": "Request Timeout",
            "answer": "408"
          },
          {
            "position": 3,
            "question": "Proxy Authentication Required",
            "answer": "407"
          },
          {
            "position": 4,
            "question": "Payment Required",
            "answer": "402"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "three": [
          {
            "position": 0,
            "question": "Locked",
            "answer": "423"
          },
          {
            "position": 1,
            "question": "Expectation Failed",
            "answer": "417"
          },
          {
            "position": 2,
            "question": "Requested Range Not Satisfiable",
            "answer": "416"
          },
          {
            "position": 3,
            "question": "Payload Too Large",
            "answer": "413"
          },
          {
            "position": 4,
            "question": "Precondition Failed",
            "answer": "412"
          },
          {
            "position": 5,
            "question": "Length Required",
            "answer": "411"
          },
          {
            "position": 6,
            "question": "Gone",
            "answer": "410"
          },
          {
            "position": 7,
            "question": "Not Acceptable",
            "answer": "406"
          },
          {
            "position": 8,
            "question": "Method Not Allowed",
            "answer": "405"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "four": [
          {
            "position": 0,
            "question": "Connection Closed Without Response",
            "answer": "444"
          },
          {
            "position": 1,
            "question": "Request Header Fields Too Large",
            "answer": "431"
          },
          {
            "position": 2,
            "question": "Too Many Requests",
            "answer": "429"
          },
          {
            "position": 3,
            "question": "Precondition Required",
            "answer": "428"
          },
          {
            "position": 4,
            "question": "Upgrade Required",
            "answer": "426"
          },
          {
            "position": 5,
            "question": "Failed Dependency",
            "answer": "424"
          },
          {
            "position": 6,
            "question": "Unprocessable Entity",
            "answer": "422"
          },
          {
            "position": 7,
            "question": "Misdirected Request",
            "answer": "421"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "five": [
          {
            "position": 0,
            "question": "Request-URI Too Long",
            "answer": "414"
          },
          {
            "position": 1,
            "question": "Client Closed Request",
            "answer": "499"
          },
          {
            "position": 2,
            "question": "Unavailable For Legal Reasons",
            "answer": "451"
          },
          {
            "position": 3,
            "question": "I'm a teapot",
            "answer": "418"
          }
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  "redirection_http_status_codes": {
    "level": [
      {
        "one": [
          {
            "position": 0,
            "question": "Moved Permanently",
            "answer": "301"
          },
          {
            "position": 1,
            "question": "Found",
            "answer": "302"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "two": [
          {
            "position": 0,
            "question": "Use Proxy",
            "answer": "305"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "three": [
          {
            "position": 0,
            "question": "Temporary Redirect",
            "answer": "307"
          },
          {
            "position": 1,
            "question": "Permanent Redirect",
            "answer": "308"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "four": [
          {
            "position": 0,
            "question": "See Other",
            "answer": "303"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "five": [
          {
            "position": 0,
            "question": "Multiple Choices",
            "answer": "300"
          },
          {
            "position": 1,
            "question": "Not Modified",
            "answer": "304"
          }
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  "javascript_types": {
    "level": [
      {
        "one": [
          {
            "position": 0,
            "question": "The BLANK type is used to represent textual data",
            "answer": "String"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "two": [
          {
            "position": 0,
            "question": "The BLANK type represents a logical entity and can have two values: true and false",
            "answer": "Boolean"
          },
          {
            "position": 1,
            "question": "The BLANK type has exactly one value: null",
            "answer": "Null"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "three": [
          {
            "position": 0,
            "question": "The BLANK type represents both integer and floating point numbers",
            "answer": "Number"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "four": [
          {
            "position": 0,
            "question": "The BLANK type has a variable that has not been assigned a value",
            "answer": "Undefined"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "five": [
          {
            "position": 0,
            "question": "The BLANK type has a unique and immutable primitive value and may be used as the key of an Object property",
            "answer": "Symbol"
          },
          {
            "position": 1,
            "question": "The BLANK type has a numeric primitive in JavaScript that can represent integers with arbitrary precision",
            "answer": "BigInt"
          }
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  "informational_and_success_http_status_codes": {
    "level": [
      {
        "one": [
          {
            "position": 0,
            "question": "Continue",
            "answer": "100"
          },
          {
            "position": 1,
            "question": "Ok",
            "answer": "200"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "two": [
          {
            "position": 0,
            "question": "Processing",
            "answer": "102"
          },
          {
            "position": 1,
            "question": "Created",
            "answer": "201"
          },
          {
            "position": 2,
            "question": "Accepted",
            "answer": "202"
          },
          {
            "position": 3,
            "question": "Reset Content",
            "answer": "205"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "three": [
          {
            "position": 0,
            "question": "Already Reported",
            "answer": "208"
          },
          {
            "position": 1,
            "question": "No Content",
            "answer": "204"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "four": [
          {
            "position": 0,
            "question": "Switching Protocols",
            "answer": "101"
          },
          {
            "position": 1,
            "question": "Partial Content",
            "answer": "206"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "five": [
          {
            "position": 0,
            "question": "Non-authoritative Information",
            "answer": "203"
          },
          {
            "position": 1,
            "question": "Multi-Status",
            "answer": "207"
          },
          {
            "position": 2,
            "question": "IM Used",
            "answer": "226"
          }
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  "python_list_methods": {
    "level": [
      {
        "one": [
          {
            "position": 0,
            "question": "The BLANK() method sorts the list",
            "answer": "sort"
          },
          {
            "position": 1,
            "question": "The BLANK() method returns the index of the first element with the specified value",
            "answer": "index"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "two": [
          {
            "position": 0,
            "question": "The BLANK() method adds an element at the end of the list",
            "answer": "append"
          },
          {
            "position": 1,
            "question": "The BLANK() method removes the element at the specified position",
            "answer": "pop"
          },
          {
            "position": 2,
            "question": "The BLANK() method reverses the order of the list",
            "answer": "reverse"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "three": [
          {
            "position": 0,
            "question": "The BLANK() method returns a copy of the list",
            "answer": "copy"
          },
          {
            "position": 1,
            "question": "The BLANK() method returns the number of elements with the specified value",
            "answer": "count"
          },
          {
            "position": 2,
            "question": "The BLANK() method adds an element at the specified position",
            "answer": "insert"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "four": [
          {
            "position": 0,
            "question": "The BLANK() method removes all the elements from the list",
            "answer": "clear"
          },
          {
            "position": 1,
            "question": "The BLANK() method removes the first item with the specified value",
            "answer": "remove"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "five": [
          {
            "position": 0,
            "question": "The BLANK() method adds the elements of a list (or any iterable), to the end of the current list",
            "answer": "extend"
          }
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  "javascript_math_methods": {
    "level": [
      {
        "one": [
          {
            "position": 0,
            "question": "The BLANK() method returns the value of a number rounded to the nearest integer ",
            "answer": "round"
          },
          {
            "position": 1,
            "question": "The BLANK() method returns the smallest of zero or more numbers",
            "answer": "min"
          },
          {
            "position": 2,
            "question": "The BLANK() method returns the largest of zero or more numbers",
            "answer": "max"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "two": [
          {
            "position": 0,
            "question": "The BLANK() method returns the square root of a number",
            "answer": "sqrt"
          },
          {
            "position": 1,
            "question": "The BLANK() method returns the largest integer less than or equal to a number",
            "answer": "floor"
          },
          {
            "position": 2,
            "question": "The BLANK() method returns the absolute value of a number",
            "answer": "abs"
          },
          {
            "position": 3,
            "question": "The BLANK() method returns a pseudo-random number between 0 and 1",
            "answer": "random"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "three": [
          {
            "position": 0,
            "question": "The BLANK() method returns the tangent of a number",
            "answer": "tan"
          },
          {
            "position": 1,
            "question": "The BLANK() method returns the cosine of a number",
            "answer": "cos"
          },
          {
            "position": 2,
            "question": "The BLANK() method returns the smallest integer greater than or equal to a number",
            "answer": "ceil"
          },
          {
            "position": 3,
            "question": "The BLANK() method returns base to the exponent power, that is, base exponent",
            "answer": "pow"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "four": [
          {
            "position": 0,
            "question": "The BLANK() method returns the arctangent of the quotient of its arguments",
            "answer": "atan2"
          },
          {
            "position": 1,
            "question": "The BLANK() method returns the arctangent (in radians) of a number",
            "answer": "atan"
          },
          {
            "position": 2,
            "question": "The BLANK() method returns the arcsine (in radians) of a number",
            "answer": "asin"
          },
          {
            "position": 3,
            "question": "The BLANK() method returns the arccosine (in radians) of a number",
            "answer": "acos"
          },
          {
            "position": 4,
            "question": "The BLANK() method returns the sine of a number",
            "answer": "sin"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "five": [
          {
            "position": 0,
            "question": "The BLANK() method returns the natural logarithm (base E) of a number",
            "answer": "log"
          },
          {
            "position": 1,
            "question": "The BLANK() method returns E^N, where N is the argument, and E is Euler's constant, the base of the natural logarithm",
            "answer": "exp"
          },
          {
            "position": 2,
            "question": "The BLANK() method returns the string 'Math'",
            "answer": "toSource"
          }
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  "python_error_types": {
    "level": [
      {
        "one": [
          {
            "position": 0,
            "question": "Raised when the assert statement fails",
            "answer": "AssertionError"
          },
          {
            "position": 1,
            "question": "Raised when the user hits the interrupt key (Ctrl+c or delete)",
            "answer": "KeyboardInterrupt"
          },
          {
            "position": 2,
            "question": "Raised when an operation runs out of memory",
            "answer": "MemoryError"
          },
          {
            "position": 3,
            "question": "Raised by the parser when a syntax error is encountered",
            "answer": "SyntaxError"
          },
          {
            "position": 4,
            "question": "Raised when a function or operation is applied to an object of an incorrect type",
            "answer": "TypeError"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "two": [
          {
            "position": 0,
            "question": "Raised when the imported module is not found",
            "answer": "ImportError"
          },
          {
            "position": 1,
            "question": "Raised on the attribute assignment or reference fails",
            "answer": "AttributeError"
          },
          {
            "position": 2,
            "question": "Raised when a function gets an argument of correct type but improper value",
            "answer": "ValueError"
          },
          {
            "position": 3,
            "question": "Raised when there is an incorrect indentation",
            "answer": "IndentationError"
          },
          {
            "position": 4,
            "question": "Raised when the index of a sequence is out of range",
            "answer": "IndexError"
          },
          {
            "position": 5,
            "question": "Raised when a weak reference proxy is used to access a garbage collected referent",
            "answer": "ReferenceError"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "three": [
          {
            "position": 0,
            "question": "Raised when a key is not found in a dictionary",
            "answer": "KeyError"
          },
          {
            "position": 1,
            "question": "Raised when a variable is not found in the local or global scope",
            "answer": "NameError"
          },
          {
            "position": 2,
            "question": "Raised by the sys.exit() function",
            "answer": "SystemExit"
          },
          {
            "position": 3,
            "question": "Raised when an application error occurs during the execution of a program",
            "answer": "RuntimeError"
          },
          {
            "position": 4,
            "question": "Raised by the next() function to indicate that there is no further item to be returned by the iterator",
            "answer": "StopIteration"
          },
          {
            "position": 5,
            "question": "Raised when the indentation consists of inconsistent tabs and spaces",
            "answer": "TabError"
          },
          {
            "position": 6,
            "question": "Raised when the interpreter detects internal error",
            "answer": "SystemError"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "four": [
          {
            "position": 0,
            "question": "Raised when a floating point operation fails",
            "answer": "FloatingPointError"
          },
          {
            "position": 1,
            "question": "Raised when a system operation causes a system-related error",
            "answer": "OSError"
          },
          {
            "position": 2,
            "question": "Raised when the result of an arithmetic operation is too large to be represented",
            "answer": "OverflowError"
          },
          {
            "position": 3,
            "question": "Raised when a Unicode-related error occurs during encoding",
            "answer": "UnicodeEncodeError"
          },
          {
            "position": 4,
            "question": "Raised when a reference is made to a local variable in a function or method, but no value has been bound to that variable",
            "answer": "UnboundLocalError"
          },
          {
            "position": 5,
            "question": "Raised when the second operand of a division or module operation is zero",
            "answer": "ZeroDivisionError"
          },
          {
            "position": 6,
            "question": "Raised when a Unicode-related error occurs during decoding",
            "answer": "UnicodeDecodeError"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "five": [
          {
            "position": 0,
            "question": "Raised when a generator's close() method is called",
            "answer": "GeneratorExit"
          },
          {
            "position": 1,
            "question": "Raised by abstract methods",
            "answer": "NotImplementedError"
          },
          {
            "position": 2,
            "question": "Raised when a Unicode-related encoding or decoding error occurs",
            "answer": "UnicodeError"
          },
          {
            "position": 3,
            "question": "Raised when a Unicode-related error occurs during translation",
            "answer": "UnicodeTranslateError"
          },
          {
            "position": 4,
            "question": "Raised when the input() function hits the end-of-file condition",
            "answer": "EOFError"
          }
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  "git_basics": {
    "level": [
      {
        "one": [
          {
            "position": 0,
            "question": "The git BLANK command is used to upload local repository content to a remote repository",
            "answer": "push"
          },
          {
            "position": 1,
            "question": "git BLANK is used to stage a file",
            "answer": "add"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "two": [
          {
            "position": 0,
            "question": "git BLANK creates a repository in Git",
            "answer": "init"
          },
          {
            "position": 1,
            "question": "git BLANK will pull files from a remote repository",
            "answer": "pull"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "three": [
          {
            "position": 0,
            "question": "git BLANK checks the status of staged files",
            "answer": "status"
          },
          {
            "position": 1,
            "question": "BLANK is a cloud-based hosting service that lets you manage Git repositories",
            "answer": "GitHub"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "four": [
          {
            "position": 0,
            "question": "git BLANK is primarily used to point to an existing repo and make a copy of that repo at in a new directory, at another location",
            "answer": "clone"
          },
          {
            "position": 1,
            "question": "BLANK is a version control system that lets you manage and keep track of your source code history",
            "answer": "Git"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "five": [
          {
            "position": 0,
            "question": "The git BLANK command is a convenience function that is used to set Git configuration values on a global or local project level",
            "answer": "config"
          },
          {
            "position": 1,
            "question": "git BLANK is used to review the repository log",
            "answer": "log"
          }
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  "cli_basics": {
    "level": [
      {
        "one": [
          {
            "position": 0,
            "question": "BLANK is the command to change the working directory",
            "answer": "cd"
          },
          {
            "position": 1,
            "question": "BLANK is the command to list contents of a directory",
            "answer": "ls"
          },
          {
            "position": 2,
            "question": "BLANK is the command to create a new directory",
            "answer": "mkdir"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "two": [
          {
            "position": 0,
            "question": "BLANK is the command to return to your home directory",
            "answer": "cd ~"
          },
          {
            "position": 1,
            "question": "BLANK is the command to return to a previous directory",
            "answer": "cd .."
          },
          {
            "position": 2,
            "question": "BLANK is the command that allows you to clear the terminal",
            "answer": "clear"
          },
          {
            "position": 3,
            "question": "BLANK is the command that allows you to do any command as an administrator (hint superuser)",
            "answer": "sudo"
          },
          {
            "position": 4,
            "question": "BLANK is the command to remove a file or directory",
            "answer": "rm"
          },
          {
            "position": 5,
            "question": "BLANK is the command line utility for printing the current working directory",
            "answer": "pwd"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "three": [
          {
            "position": 0,
            "question": "BLANK is the command to view the history or previous commands",
            "answer": "history"
          },
          {
            "position": 1,
            "question": "BLANK is the command that allows you to copy a file or directory",
            "answer": "cp"
          },
          {
            "position": 2,
            "question": "BLANK is the command to move a file or directory",
            "answer": "mv"
          },
          {
            "position": 3,
            "question": "BLANK is the key that allows you to autocomplete",
            "answer": "tab"
          },
          {
            "position": 4,
            "question": "ctrl BLANK will force quit a process",
            "answer": "C"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "four": [
          {
            "position": 0,
            "question": "BLANK is the command that will allow you to view manual",
            "answer": "man"
          },
          {
            "position": 1,
            "question": "ctrl BLANK will reverse search through your history",
            "answer": "r"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "five": [
          {
            "position": 0,
            "question": "BLANK is the command to search a file or directory",
            "answer": "grep"
          },
          {
            "position": 1,
            "question": "ctrl BLANK allows you to exit (common on interactive interfaces, example: python)",
            "answer": "d"
          },
          {
            "position": 2,
            "question": "BLANK is the command that interactively show contents of a file",
            "answer": "less"
          },
          {
            "position": 3,
            "question": "BLANK is the command to dump contents of a file to output",
            "answer": "cat"
          }
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  "sql_keywords": {
    "level": [
      {
        "one": [
          {
            "position": 0,
            "question": "Inserts new rows in a table",
            "answer": "INSERT INTO"
          },
          {
            "position": 1,
            "question": "Filters a result set to include only records that fulfill a specified condition",
            "answer": "WHERE"
          },
          {
            "position": 2,
            "question": "Updates existing rows in a table",
            "answer": "UPDATE"
          },
          {
            "position": 3,
            "question": "Creates a new SQL database",
            "answer": "CREATE DATABASE"
          },
          {
            "position": 4,
            "question": "Selects data from a database",
            "answer": "SELECT"
          },
          {
            "position": 5,
            "question": "Specifies which table to select or delete data from",
            "answer": "FROM"
          },
          {
            "position": 6,
            "question": "Adds a column in an existing table",
            "answer": "ADD"
          },
          {
            "position": 7,
            "question": "Deletes an existing SQL database",
            "answer": "DROP DATABASE"
          },
          {
            "position": 8,
            "question": "Creates a database, index, view, table, or procedure",
            "answer": "CREATE"
          },
          {
            "position": 9,
            "question": "Deletes rows from a table",
            "answer": "DELETE"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "two": [
          {
            "position": 0,
            "question": "Adds, deletes, or modifies columns in a table, or changes the data type of a column in a table",
            "answer": "ALTER"
          },
          {
            "position": 1,
            "question": "Changes the data type of a column in a table",
            "answer": "ALTER COLUMN"
          },
          {
            "position": 2,
            "question": "Adds, deletes, or modifies columns in a table",
            "answer": "ALTER TABLE"
          },
          {
            "position": 3,
            "question": "Deletes a column, constraint, database, index, table, or view",
            "answer": "DROP"
          },
          {
            "position": 4,
            "question": "Creates an index on a table (allows duplicate values)",
            "answer": "CREATE INDEX"
          },
          {
            "position": 5,
            "question": "Includes rows where either condition is true",
            "answer": "OR"
          },
          {
            "position": 6,
            "question": "Sorts the result set in ascending or descending order",
            "answer": "ORDER BY"
          },
          {
            "position": 7,
            "question": "Creates a table, or adds, deletes, or modifies columns in a table, or deletes a table or data inside a table",
            "answer": "TABLE"
          },
          {
            "position": 8,
            "question": "A constraint that ensures that all values in a column are unique",
            "answer": "UNIQUE"
          },
          {
            "position": 9,
            "question": "A constraint that uniquely identifies each record in a database table",
            "answer": "PRIMARY KEY"
          },
          {
            "position": 10,
            "question": "Specifies the values of an INSERT INTO statement",
            "answer": "VALUES"
          },
          {
            "position": 11,
            "question": "Joins tables",
            "answer": "JOIN"
          },
          {
            "position": 12,
            "question": "Deletes a column in a table",
            "answer": "DROP COLUMNL"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "three": [
          {
            "position": 0,
            "question": "Only includes rows where both conditions is true",
            "answer": "AND"
          },
          {
            "position": 1,
            "question": "Renames a column or table with an alias",
            "answer": "AS"
          },
          {
            "position": 2,
            "question": "Sorts the result set in ascending order",
            "answer": "ASC"
          },
          {
            "position": 3,
            "question": "Selects values within a given range",
            "answer": "BETWEEN"
          },
          {
            "position": 4,
            "question": "A constraint that provides a default value for a column",
            "answer": "DEFAULT"
          },
          {
            "position": 5,
            "question": "Changes the data type of a column or deletes a column in a table",
            "answer": "COLUMN"
          },
          {
            "position": 6,
            "question": "Groups the result set (used with aggregate functions: COUNT, MAX, MIN, SUM, AVG)",
            "answer": "GROUP BY"
          },
          {
            "position": 7,
            "question": "Deletes a UNIQUE, PRIMARY KEY, FOREIGN KEY, or CHECK constraint",
            "answer": "DROP CONSTRAINT"
          },
          {
            "position": 8,
            "question": "Creates or deletes an index in a table",
            "answer": "INDEX"
          },
          {
            "position": 9,
            "question": "Creates a new table in the database",
            "answer": "CREATE TABLE"
          },
          {
            "position": 10,
            "question": "Deletes a view",
            "answer": "DROP VIEW"
          },
          {
            "position": 11,
            "question": "Deletes an existing table in the database",
            "answer": "DROP TABLE"
          },
          {
            "position": 12,
            "question": "Deletes an index in a table",
            "answer": "DROP INDEX"
          },
          {
            "position": 13,
            "question": "A constraint that is a key used to link two tables together",
            "answer": "FOREIGN KEY"
          },
          {
            "position": 14,
            "question": "Deletes a DEFAULT constraint",
            "answer": "DROP DEFAULT"
          },
          {
            "position": 15,
            "question": "Selects only distinct (different) values",
            "answer": "SELECT DISTINCT"
          },
          {
            "position": 16,
            "question": "A constraint that enforces a column to not accept NULL values",
            "answer": "NOT NULL"
          },
          {
            "position": 17,
            "question": "Only includes rows where a condition is not true",
            "answer": "NOT"
          },
          {
            "position": 18,
            "question": "Specifies the number of records to return in the result set",
            "answer": "LIMIT"
          },
          {
            "position": 19,
            "question": "Returns all rows from the left table, and the matching rows from the right table",
            "answer": "LEFT JOIN"
          },
          {
            "position": 20,
            "question": "Tests for non-empty values",
            "answer": "IS NOT NULL"
          },
          {
            "position": 21,
            "question": "Tests for empty values",
            "answer": "IS NULL"
          },
          {
            "position": 22,
            "question": "Copies data from one table into another table",
            "answer": "INSERT INTO SELECT"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "four": [
          {
            "position": 0,
            "question": "Adds a constraint after a table is already created",
            "answer": "ADD CONSTRAINT"
          },
          {
            "position": 1,
            "question": "Returns true if all of the subquery values meet the condition",
            "answer": "ALL"
          },
          {
            "position": 2,
            "question": "Returns true if any of the subquery values meet the condition",
            "answer": "ANY"
          },
          {
            "position": 3,
            "question": "Creates a back up of an existing database",
            "answer": "BACKUP DATABASE"
          },
          {
            "position": 4,
            "question": "Creates different outputs based on conditions",
            "answer": "CASE"
          },
          {
            "position": 5,
            "question": "Adds or deletes a constraint",
            "answer": "CONSTRAINT"
          },
          {
            "position": 6,
            "question": "Updates a view",
            "answer": "REPLACE VIEW"
          },
          {
            "position": 7,
            "question": "Creates a stored procedure",
            "answer": "CREATE PROCEDURE"
          },
          {
            "position": 8,
            "question": "Creates a view based on the result set of a SELECT statement",
            "answer": "CREATE VIEW"
          },
          {
            "position": 9,
            "question": "Allows you to specify multiple values in a WHERE clause",
            "answer": "IN"
          },
          {
            "position": 10,
            "question": "Sorts the result set in descending order",
            "answer": "DESC"
          },
          {
            "position": 11,
            "question": "Copies data from one table into a new table",
            "answer": "SELECT INTO"
          },
          {
            "position": 12,
            "question": "Returns rows that have matching values in both tables",
            "answer": "INNER JOIN"
          },
          {
            "position": 13,
            "question": "Creates, updates, or deletes a view",
            "answer": "VIEW"
          },
          {
            "position": 14,
            "question": "Specifies which columns and values that should be updated in a table",
            "answer": "SET"
          },
          {
            "position": 15,
            "question": "Returns all rows from the right table, and the matching rows from the left table",
            "answer": "RIGHT JOIN"
          },
          {
            "position": 16,
            "question": "Searches for a specified pattern in a column",
            "answer": "LIKE"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "five": [
          {
            "position": 0,
            "question": "Selects only distinct (different) values",
            "answer": "DISTINCT"
          },
          {
            "position": 1,
            "question": "Creates a unique index on a table (no duplicate values)",
            "answer": "CREATE UNIQUE INDEX"
          },
          {
            "position": 2,
            "question": "A constraint that limits the value that can be placed in a column",
            "answer": "CHECK"
          },
          {
            "position": 3,
            "question": "Combines the result set of two or more SELECT statements (allows duplicate values)",
            "answer": "UNION ALL"
          },
          {
            "position": 4,
            "question": "Combines the result set of two or more SELECT statements (only distinct values)",
            "answer": "UNION"
          },
          {
            "position": 5,
            "question": "Deletes the data inside a table, but not the table itself",
            "answer": "TRUNCATE TABLE"
          },
          {
            "position": 6,
            "question": "Used instead of WHERE with aggregate functions",
            "answer": "HAVING"
          },
          {
            "position": 7,
            "question": "A stored procedure",
            "answer": "PROCEDURE"
          },
          {
            "position": 8,
            "question": "Tests for the existence of any record in a subquery",
            "answer": "EXISTS"
          },
          {
            "position": 9,
            "question": "Executes a stored procedure",
            "answer": "EXEC"
          }
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  "javascript_string_methods": {
    "level": [
      {
        "one": [
          {
            "position": 0,
            "question": "The BLANK method returns  the length of a string",
            "answer": "length"
          },
          {
            "position": 1,
            "question": "The BLANK method returns  the string's constructor function",
            "answer": "constructor"
          },
          {
            "position": 2,
            "question": "The BLANK() method returns two or more joined strings",
            "answer": "concat"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "two": [
          {
            "position": 0,
            "question": "The BLANK() method returns  a string converted to uppercase letters",
            "answer": "toUpperCase"
          },
          {
            "position": 1,
            "question": "The BLANK() method returns  a string converted to lowercase letters",
            "answer": "toLowerCase"
          },
          {
            "position": 2,
            "question": "The BLANK() method splits a string into an array of substrings",
            "answer": "split"
          },
          {
            "position": 3,
            "question": "The BLANK() method extracts a part of a string and returns a new string",
            "answer": "slice"
          },
          {
            "position": 4,
            "question": "The BLANK() method searches a string for a value, or a regular expression, and returns a string where the values are replaced",
            "answer": "replace"
          },
          {
            "position": 5,
            "question": "The BLANK() method returns a string or a string object as a string",
            "answer": "toString"
          },
          {
            "position": 6,
            "question": "The BLANK() method returns the index (position) of the first occurrence of a value in a string",
            "answer": "indexOf"
          },
          {
            "position": 7,
            "question": "The BLANK() method returns if a string contains a specified value",
            "answer": "includes"
          },
          {
            "position": 8,
            "question": "The BLANK() method returns the character at a specified index (position)",
            "answer": "charAt"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "three": [
          {
            "position": 0,
            "question": "The BLANK() method returns the primitive value of a string or a string object",
            "answer": "valueOf"
          },
          {
            "position": 1,
            "question": "The BLANK() method searches a string for a value, or regular expression, and returns the index (position) of the match",
            "answer": "search"
          },
          {
            "position": 2,
            "question": "The BLANK() method returns  a new string with a number of copies of a string",
            "answer": "repeat"
          },
          {
            "position": 3,
            "question": "The BLANK() method returns  if a string ends with a specified value",
            "answer": "endsWith"
          },
          {
            "position": 4,
            "question": "The BLANK() method returns  the index (position) of the last occurrence of a value in a string",
            "answer": "lastIndexOf"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "four": [
          {
            "position": 0,
            "question": "The BLANK() method searches a string for a value, or a regular expression, and returns the matches",
            "answer": "match"
          },
          {
            "position": 1,
            "question": "The BLANK method allows you to add properties and methods to an object",
            "answer": "prototype"
          },
          {
            "position": 2,
            "question": "The BLANK() method checks whether a string begins with specified characters",
            "answer": "startsWith"
          },
          {
            "position": 3,
            "question": "The BLANK() method extracts a number of characters from a string, from a start index (position)",
            "answer": "substr"
          },
          {
            "position": 4,
            "question": "The BLANK() method extracts characters from a string, between two specified indices (positions)",
            "answer": "substring"
          },
          {
            "position": 5,
            "question": "The BLANK() method returns a string with removed whitespaces",
            "answer": "trim"
          },
          {
            "position": 6,
            "question": "The BLANK() method returns a string with removed whitespaces from the end",
            "answer": "trimEnd"
          },
          {
            "position": 7,
            "question": "The BLANK() method returns a string with removed whitespaces from the start",
            "answer": "trimStart"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "five": [
          {
            "position": 0,
            "question": "The BLANK() method returns Unicode values as characters",
            "answer": "fromCharCode"
          },
          {
            "position": 1,
            "question": "The BLANK() method compares two strings in the current locale",
            "answer": "localeCompare"
          },
          {
            "position": 2,
            "question": "The BLANK() method returns the Unicode of the character at a specified index",
            "answer": "charCodeAt"
          },
          {
            "position": 3,
            "question": "The BLANK() method returns a string converted to lowercase letters, using the host's locale",
            "answer": "toLocaleLowerCase"
          },
          {
            "position": 4,
            "question": "The BLANK() method returns a string converted to uppercase letters, using the host's locale",
            "answer": "toLocaleUpperCase"
          }
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  "sorting_algorithms": {
    "level": [
      {
        "one": [
          {
            "position": 0,
            "question": "BLANK Sort is the simplest sorting algorithm that works by repeatedly swapping the adjacent elements if they are in the wrong order. This algorithm is not suitable for large data sets as its average and worst-case time complexity is quite high.",
            "answer": "Bubble"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "two": [
          {
            "position": 0,
            "question": "BLANK sort is a simple sorting algorithm that works similar to the way you sort playing cards in your hands. The array is virtually split into a sorted and an unsorted part. Values from the unsorted part are picked and placed at the correct position in the sorted part.",
            "answer": "Insertion"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "three": [
          {
            "position": 0,
            "question": "BLANK sort is a simple and efficient sorting algorithm that works by repeatedly selecting the smallest (or largest) element from the unsorted portion of the list and moving it to the sorted portion of the list. The algorithm repeatedly selects the smallest (or largest) element from the unsorted portion of the list and swaps it with the first element of the unsorted portion. This process is repeated for the remaining unsorted portion of the list until the entire list is sorted.",
            "answer": "Selection"
          },
          {
            "position": 1,
            "question": "BLANK sort is a sorting technique based on keys between a specific range. It works by counting the number of objects having distinct key values (a kind of hashing). Then do some arithmetic operations to calculate the position of each object in the output sequence.",
            "answer": "Counting"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "four": [
          {
            "position": 0,
            "question": "BLANK sort is a sorting algorithm that works by dividing an array into smaller subarrays, sorting each subarray, and then merging the sorted subarrays back together to form the final sorted array.",
            "answer": "Merge"
          },
          {
            "position": 1,
            "question": "BLANK sort is a sorting algorithm that sequences a list by continuously dividing the list into two parts and moving the lower items to one side and the higher items to the other. It starts by picking one item in the entire list to serve as a pivot point. The pivot could be the first item or a randomly chosen one. All items that compare lower than the pivot are moved to the left of the pivot; all equal or higher items are moved to the right. It then picks a pivot for the left side and moves those items to left and right of the pivot and continues the pivot picking and dividing until there is only one item left in the group. It then proceeds to the right side and performs the same operation again.",
            "answer": "Quick"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "five": [
          {
            "position": 0,
            "question": "BLANK sort is a popular and efficient sorting algorithm. The concept of BLANK sort is to eliminate the elements one by one from the heap part of the list, and then insert them into the sorted part of the list.",
            "answer": "Heap"
          },
          {
            "position": 1,
            "question": "BLANK sort is an integer sorting algorithm that sorts data with integer keys by grouping the keys by individual digits that share the same significant position and value (place value). Radix sort uses counting sort as a subroutine to sort an array of numbers.",
            "answer": "Radix"
          }
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  "javascript_date_methods_and_properties": {
    "level": [
      {
        "one": [
          {
            "position": 0,
            "question": "BLANK() returns the day of the month (from 1-31)",
            "answer": "getUTCDate"
          },
          {
            "position": 1,
            "question": "BLANK() returns the day of the week (from 0-6)",
            "answer": "getDay"
          },
          {
            "position": 2,
            "question": "BLANK() converts a Date object to a string",
            "answer": "toString"
          },
          {
            "position": 3,
            "question": "BLANK() sets the day of the month of a date object",
            "answer": "setDate"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "two": [
          {
            "position": 0,
            "question": "BLANK() sets the seconds of a date object",
            "answer": "setSeconds"
          },
          {
            "position": 1,
            "question": "BLANK() sets the month of a date object",
            "answer": "setMonth"
          },
          {
            "position": 2,
            "question": "BLANK() sets the minutes of a date object",
            "answer": "setMinutes"
          },
          {
            "position": 3,
            "question": "BLANK() sets the milliseconds of a date object",
            "answer": "setMilliseconds"
          },
          {
            "position": 4,
            "question": "BLANK() sets the hour of a date object",
            "answer": "setHours"
          },
          {
            "position": 5,
            "question": "BLANK() returns the month (from 0-11)",
            "answer": "getMonth"
          },
          {
            "position": 6,
            "question": "BLANK() returns the minutes (from 0-59)",
            "answer": "getMinutes"
          },
          {
            "position": 7,
            "question": "BLANK() returns the hour (from 0-23)",
            "answer": "getHours"
          },
          {
            "position": 8,
            "question": "BLANK() returns the milliseconds (from 0-999)",
            "answer": "getMilliseconds"
          },
          {
            "position": 9,
            "question": "BLANK() returns the seconds (from 0-59)",
            "answer": "getSeconds"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "three": [
          {
            "position": 0,
            "question": "BLANK returns the function that created the Date object's prototype",
            "answer": "constructor"
          },
          {
            "position": 1,
            "question": "BLANK() sets the year of a date object",
            "answer": "setFullYear"
          },
          {
            "position": 2,
            "question": "BLANK() converts the date portion of a Date object into a readable string",
            "answer": "toDateString"
          },
          {
            "position": 3,
            "question": "BLANK() parses a date string and BLANK() returns the number of milliseconds since January 1, 1970",
            "answer": "parse"
          },
          {
            "position": 4,
            "question": "BLANK() returns the year",
            "answer": "getFullYear"
          },
          {
            "position": 5,
            "question": "BLANK() returns the date as a string, formatted as a JSON date",
            "answer": "toJSON"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "four": [
          {
            "position": 0,
            "question": "BLANK() returns the primitive value of a Date object",
            "answer": "valueOf"
          },
          {
            "position": 1,
            "question": "BLANK() converts the time portion of a Date object to a string",
            "answer": "toTimeString"
          },
          {
            "position": 2,
            "question": "BLANK() converts a Date object to a string, using locale conventions",
            "answer": "toLocaleString"
          },
          {
            "position": 3,
            "question": "BLANK() returns the time portion of a Date object as a string, using locale conventions",
            "answer": "toLocaleTimeString"
          },
          {
            "position": 4,
            "question": "BLANK() returns the date portion of a Date object as a string, using locale conventions",
            "answer": "toLocaleDateString"
          },
          {
            "position": 5,
            "question": "BLANK() returns the number of milliseconds since midnight Jan 1, 1970",
            "answer": "now"
          },
          {
            "position": 6,
            "question": "BLANK() sets a date to a specified number of milliseconds after/before January 1, 1970",
            "answer": "setTime"
          },
          {
            "position": 7,
            "question": "BLANK allows you to add properties and methods to an object",
            "answer": "prototype"
          },
          {
            "position": 8,
            "question": "BLANK() returns the number of milliseconds since midnight Jan 1 1970, and a specified date",
            "answer": "getTime"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "five": [
          {
            "position": 0,
            "question": "BLANK() returns the date as a string, using the ISO standard",
            "answer": "toISOString"
          },
          {
            "position": 1,
            "question": "BLANK() returns the number of milliseconds in a date since midnight of January 1, 1970, according to UTC time",
            "answer": "UTC"
          },
          {
            "position": 2,
            "question": "BLANK() sets the seconds of a date object, according to universal time",
            "answer": "setUTCSeconds"
          },
          {
            "position": 3,
            "question": "BLANK() sets the month of a date object, according to universal time",
            "answer": "setUTCMonth"
          },
          {
            "position": 4,
            "question": "BLANK() converts a Date object to a string, according to universal time",
            "answer": "toUTCString"
          },
          {
            "position": 5,
            "question": "BLANK() sets the minutes of a date object, according to universal time",
            "answer": "setUTCMinutes"
          },
          {
            "position": 6,
            "question": "BLANK() sets the milliseconds of a date object, according to universal time",
            "answer": "setUTCMilliseconds"
          },
          {
            "position": 7,
            "question": "BLANK() sets the hour of a date object, according to universal time",
            "answer": "setUTCHours"
          },
          {
            "position": 8,
            "question": "BLANK() sets the year of a date object, according to universal time",
            "answer": "setUTCFullYear"
          },
          {
            "position": 9,
            "question": "BLANK() sets the day of the month of a date object, according to universal time",
            "answer": "setUTCDate"
          },
          {
            "position": 10,
            "question": "BLANK() returns the seconds, according to universal time (from 0-59)",
            "answer": "getUTCSeconds"
          },
          {
            "position": 11,
            "question": "BLANK() returns the month, according to universal time (from 0-11)",
            "answer": "getUTCMonth"
          },
          {
            "position": 12,
            "question": "BLANK() returns the minutes, according to universal time (from 0-59)",
            "answer": "getUTCMinutes"
          },
          {
            "position": 13,
            "question": "BLANK() returns the milliseconds, according to universal time (from 0-999)",
            "answer": "getUTCMilliseconds"
          },
          {
            "position": 14,
            "question": "BLANK() returns the hour, according to universal time (from 0-23)",
            "answer": "getUTCHours"
          },
          {
            "position": 15,
            "question": "BLANK() returns the year, according to universal time",
            "answer": "getUTCFullYear"
          },
          {
            "position": 16,
            "question": "BLANK() returns the day of the week, according to universal time (from 0-6)",
            "answer": "getUTCDay"
          },
          {
            "position": 17,
            "question": "BLANK() returns the day of the month, according to universal time (from 1-31)",
            "answer": "getUTCDate"
          },
          {
            "position": 18,
            "question": "BLANK() returns the time difference between UTC time and local time, in minutes",
            "answer": "getTimezoneOffset"
          }
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  "redux": {
    "level": [
      {
        "one": [
          {
            "position": 0,
            "question": "To change something in the state, you need to dispatch a/an BLANK. A/An BLANK is a plain JavaScript object that describes what happened.",
            "answer": "Action"
          },
          {
            "position": 1,
            "question": "BLANK is a predictable state container for JavaScript apps.",
            "answer": "Redux"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "two": [
          {
            "position": 0,
            "question": "BLANK() returns the current state tree of your application. It is equal to the last value returned by the store's reducer.",
            "answer": "getState"
          },
          {
            "position": 1,
            "question": "A/An BLANK is a pure function that takes an action and the previous state of the application and returns the new state.",
            "answer": "reducer"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "three": [
          {
            "position": 0,
            "question": "BLANK(listener) adds a change listener.",
            "answer": "subscribe"
          },
          {
            "position": 1,
            "question": "BLANK(action). This is the only way to trigger a state change.",
            "answer": "Dispatch"
          },
          {
            "position": 2,
            "question": "A/An BLANK is an immutable object tree in Redux. A/An BLANK is a state container which holds the application's state.",
            "answer": "Store"
          },
          {
            "position": 3,
            "question": "The <BLANK> component makes the Redux store available to any nested components that need to access the Redux store.",
            "answer": "Provider"
          },
          {
            "position": 4,
            "question": "BLANK is a description or template for how to solve a problem that can be used in many different situations.",
            "answer": "software design pattern"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "four": [
          {
            "position": 0,
            "question": "BLANK(nextReducer) replaces the reducer currently used by the store to calculate the state.",
            "answer": "replaceReducer"
          },
          {
            "position": 1,
            "question": "BLANK are the primary components and the entry point from which we call child or generic components.",
            "answer": "Containers"
          },
          {
            "position": 2,
            "question": "BLANK does exactly what its name suggests: it connects a part of the Redux state to the props of a React component. By doing so a connected React component will have access to the exact part of the store it needs.",
            "answer": "mapStateToProps"
          },
          {
            "position": 3,
            "question": "In THE 'BLANK' pattern, senders of messages called publishers, do not program the messages to be sent directly to specific receivers, called subscribers",
            "answer": "Publisher-Subscriber"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "five": [
          {
            "position": 0,
            "question": "BLANK design patterns provide a way to create objects while hiding the creation logic, rather than instantiating objects directly using new operator. This gives program more flexibility in deciding which objects need to be created for a given use case.",
            "answer": "Creational"
          },
          {
            "position": 1,
            "question": "The BLANK pattern is a software design pattern in which an object, called the subject, maintains a list of its dependents, called observers, and notifies them automatically of any state changes, usually by calling one of their methods.",
            "answer": "Observer"
          },
          {
            "position": 2,
            "question": "BLANK design patterns are specifically concerned with the presentation tier. These patterns are identified by Sun Java Center.",
            "answer": "J2EE"
          },
          {
            "position": 3,
            "question": "BLANK design patterns are specifically concerned with communication between objects.",
            "answer": "Behavioral"
          },
          {
            "position": 4,
            "question": "BLANK design patterns concern class and object composition. Concept of inheritance is used to compose interfaces and define ways to compose objects to obtain new functionalities.",
            "answer": "Structural"
          }
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  "css": {
    "level": [
      {
        "one": [
          {
            "position": 0,
            "question": "Sets the top margin of an element",
            "answer": "margin-top"
          },
          {
            "position": 1,
            "question": "Sets the bottom margin of an element",
            "answer": "margin-bottom"
          },
          {
            "position": 2,
            "question": "Sets all the margin properties in one declaration",
            "answer": "margin"
          },
          {
            "position": 3,
            "question": "Specifies the size of the background images",
            "answer": "background-size"
          },
          {
            "position": 4,
            "question": "Sets the height of an element",
            "answer": "height"
          },
          {
            "position": 5,
            "question": "Sets the color of the four borders",
            "answer": "border-color"
          },
          {
            "position": 6,
            "question": "Sets the width of the four borders",
            "answer": "border-width"
          },
          {
            "position": 7,
            "question": "Sets the width of the top border",
            "answer": "border-top-width"
          },
          {
            "position": 8,
            "question": "Sets the color of text",
            "answer": "color"
          },
          {
            "position": 9,
            "question": "Specifies the weight of a font",
            "answer": "font-weight"
          },
          {
            "position": 10,
            "question": "Specifies the font style for text",
            "answer": "font-style"
          },
          {
            "position": 11,
            "question": "Specifies the font family for text",
            "answer": "font-family"
          },
          {
            "position": 12,
            "question": "Sets the width of an element",
            "answer": "width"
          },
          {
            "position": 13,
            "question": "A shorthand property for the font-style, font-variant, font-weight, font-size/line-height, and the font-family properties",
            "answer": "font"
          },
          {
            "position": 14,
            "question": "Specifies the font size of text",
            "answer": "font-size"
          },
          {
            "position": 15,
            "question": "A shorthand property for border-width, border-style and border-color",
            "answer": "border"
          },
          {
            "position": 16,
            "question": "Sets if/how a background image will be repeated",
            "answer": "background-repeat"
          },
          {
            "position": 17,
            "question": "Specifies the position of a background image",
            "answer": "background-position"
          },
          {
            "position": 18,
            "question": "Specifies one or more background images for an element",
            "answer": "background-image"
          },
          {
            "position": 19,
            "question": "Specifies the background color of an element",
            "answer": "background-color"
          },
          {
            "position": 20,
            "question": "A shorthand property for all the background-* properties",
            "answer": "background"
          },
          {
            "position": 21,
            "question": "A shorthand property for all the padding-* properties",
            "answer": "padding"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "two": [
          {
            "position": 0,
            "question": "Specifies the decoration added to text",
            "answer": "text-decoration"
          },
          {
            "position": 1,
            "question": "Specifies the color of the text-decoration",
            "answer": "text-decoration-color"
          },
          {
            "position": 2,
            "question": "Specifies the type of line in a text-decoration",
            "answer": "text-decoration-line"
          },
          {
            "position": 3,
            "question": "Specifies the style of the line in a text decoration",
            "answer": "text-decoration-style"
          },
          {
            "position": 4,
            "question": "Specifies the thickness of the decoration line",
            "answer": "text-decoration-thickness"
          },
          {
            "position": 5,
            "question": "Applies emphasis marks to text",
            "answer": "text-emphasis"
          },
          {
            "position": 6,
            "question": "Specifies what should happen when text overflows the containing element",
            "answer": "text-overflow"
          },
          {
            "position": 7,
            "question": "Specifies the indentation of the first line in a text-block",
            "answer": "text-indent"
          },
          {
            "position": 8,
            "question": "Controls the capitalization of text",
            "answer": "text-transform"
          },
          {
            "position": 9,
            "question": "Sets the vertical alignment of an element",
            "answer": "vertical-align"
          },
          {
            "position": 10,
            "question": "Specifies the position of the underline which is set using the text-decoration property",
            "answer": "text-underline-position"
          },
          {
            "position": 11,
            "question": "Sets the opacity level for an element",
            "answer": "opacity"
          },
          {
            "position": 12,
            "question": "Sets the line height",
            "answer": "line-height"
          },
          {
            "position": 13,
            "question": "Specifies whether an element should float to the left, right, or not at all",
            "answer": "float"
          },
          {
            "position": 14,
            "question": "Specifies the position of a background image on y-axis",
            "answer": "background-position-y"
          },
          {
            "position": 15,
            "question": "A shorthand property for all the animation-* properties",
            "answer": "animation"
          },
          {
            "position": 16,
            "question": "Sets the width of an outline",
            "answer": "outline-width"
          },
          {
            "position": 17,
            "question": "Sets the color of an outline",
            "answer": "outline-color"
          },
          {
            "position": 18,
            "question": "A shorthand property for the outline-width, outline-style, and the outline-color properties",
            "answer": "outline"
          },
          {
            "position": 19,
            "question": "Sets the minimum width of an element",
            "answer": "min-width"
          },
          {
            "position": 20,
            "question": "Specifies the right position of a positioned element",
            "answer": "right"
          },
          {
            "position": 21,
            "question": "Sets the top padding of an element",
            "answer": "padding-top"
          },
          {
            "position": 22,
            "question": "Sets the right padding of an element",
            "answer": "padding-right"
          },
          {
            "position": 23,
            "question": "Sets the left padding of an element",
            "answer": "padding-left"
          },
          {
            "position": 24,
            "question": "Specifies the padding in the block direction",
            "answer": "padding-block"
          },
          {
            "position": 25,
            "question": "Specifies the padding in the inline direction",
            "answer": "padding-inline"
          },
          {
            "position": 26,
            "question": "Sets the bottom padding of an element",
            "answer": "padding-bottom"
          },
          {
            "position": 27,
            "question": "Sets the minimum height of an element",
            "answer": "min-height"
          },
          {
            "position": 28,
            "question": "Sets the style rules for different media types/devices/sizes",
            "answer": "media"
          },
          {
            "position": 29,
            "question": "Sets the maximum width of an element",
            "answer": "max-width"
          },
          {
            "position": 30,
            "question": "Sets the maximum height of an element",
            "answer": "max-height"
          },
          {
            "position": 31,
            "question": "Specifies how/if to break lines",
            "answer": "line-break"
          },
          {
            "position": 32,
            "question": "Sets the right margin of an element",
            "answer": "margin-right"
          },
          {
            "position": 33,
            "question": "Sets the left margin of an element",
            "answer": "margin-left"
          },
          {
            "position": 34,
            "question": "Specifies the left position of a positioned element",
            "answer": "left"
          },
          {
            "position": 35,
            "question": "@BLANK allows you to import a style sheet into another style sheet",
            "answer": "import"
          },
          {
            "position": 36,
            "question": "Specifies the margin at the start in the block direction",
            "answer": "margin-block-start"
          },
          {
            "position": 37,
            "question": "Specifies the margin at the end in the block direction",
            "answer": "margin-block-end"
          },
          {
            "position": 38,
            "question": "Specifies the margin in the block direction",
            "answer": "margin-block"
          },
          {
            "position": 39,
            "question": "A shorthand property for the grid-template-rows, grid-template-columns and grid-areas properties",
            "answer": "grid-template"
          },
          {
            "position": 40,
            "question": "Specifies the direction of the flexible items",
            "answer": "flex-direction"
          },
          {
            "position": 41,
            "question": "A shorthand property for the grid-template-rows, grid-template-columns, grid-template-areas, grid-auto-rows, grid-auto-columns, and the grid-auto-flow properties",
            "answer": "grid"
          },
          {
            "position": 42,
            "question": "A shorthand property for the flex-grow, flex-shrink, and the flex-basis properties",
            "answer": "flex"
          },
          {
            "position": 43,
            "question": "Specifies the position of a background image on x-axis",
            "answer": "background-position-x"
          },
          {
            "position": 44,
            "question": "Specifies the origin position of a background image",
            "answer": "background-origin"
          },
          {
            "position": 45,
            "question": "Sets whether a background image scrolls with the rest of the page, or is fixed",
            "answer": "background-attachment"
          },
          {
            "position": 46,
            "question": "Specifies preferred aspect ratio of an element",
            "answer": "aspect-ratio"
          },
          {
            "position": 47,
            "question": "Specifies the alignment for selected items inside a flexible container",
            "answer": "align-self"
          },
          {
            "position": 48,
            "question": "Specifies the alignment for items inside a flexible container",
            "answer": "align-items"
          },
          {
            "position": 49,
            "question": "Specifies the alignment between the lines inside a flexible container when the items do not use all available space",
            "answer": "align-content"
          },
          {
            "position": 50,
            "question": "Sets the style of the top border",
            "answer": "border-top-style"
          },
          {
            "position": 51,
            "question": "Sets the width of the left border",
            "answer": "border-left-width"
          },
          {
            "position": 52,
            "question": "Sets the color of the left border",
            "answer": "border-left-color"
          },
          {
            "position": 53,
            "question": "Sets the color of the top border",
            "answer": "border-top-color"
          },
          {
            "position": 54,
            "question": "A shorthand property for border-top-width, border-top-style and border-top-color",
            "answer": "border-top"
          },
          {
            "position": 55,
            "question": "Sets the style of the four borders",
            "answer": "border-style"
          },
          {
            "position": 56,
            "question": "Specifies the gap between the columns",
            "answer": "column-gap"
          },
          {
            "position": 57,
            "question": "Sets the width of the right border",
            "answer": "border-right-width"
          },
          {
            "position": 58,
            "question": "Sets the style of the right border",
            "answer": "border-right-style"
          },
          {
            "position": 59,
            "question": "Sets the color of the right border",
            "answer": "border-right-color"
          },
          {
            "position": 60,
            "question": "A shorthand property for all the border-right-* properties",
            "answer": "border-right"
          },
          {
            "position": 61,
            "question": "A shorthand property for all the border-left-* properties",
            "answer": "border-left"
          },
          {
            "position": 62,
            "question": "Sets the color of the borders at start and end in the inline direction",
            "answer": "border-inline-color"
          },
          {
            "position": 63,
            "question": "A shorthand property for border-inline-width, border-inline-style and border-inline-color",
            "answer": "border-inline"
          },
          {
            "position": 64,
            "question": "Specifies the width of the border image",
            "answer": "border-image-width"
          },
          {
            "position": 65,
            "question": "A shorthand property for all the border-image-* properties",
            "answer": "border-image"
          },
          {
            "position": 66,
            "question": "Sets the width of the bottom border",
            "answer": "border-bottom-width"
          },
          {
            "position": 67,
            "question": "Sets the color of the bottom border",
            "answer": "border-bottom-color"
          },
          {
            "position": 68,
            "question": "A shorthand property for border-bottom-width, border-bottom-style and border-bottom-color",
            "answer": "border-bottom"
          },
          {
            "position": 69,
            "question": "Specifies the horizontal alignment of text",
            "answer": "text-align"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "three": [
          {
            "position": 0,
            "question": "Specifies the size of an element in block direction",
            "answer": "block-size"
          },
          {
            "position": 1,
            "question": "A shorthand property for border-block-width, border-block-style and border-block-color",
            "answer": "border-block"
          },
          {
            "position": 2,
            "question": "Specifies the blending mode of each background layer (color/image)",
            "answer": "background-blend-mode"
          },
          {
            "position": 3,
            "question": "Sets the style of the bottom border",
            "answer": "border-bottom-style"
          },
          {
            "position": 4,
            "question": "Sets whether table borders should collapse into a single border or be separated",
            "answer": "border-collapse"
          },
          {
            "position": 5,
            "question": "Specifies whether the border image should be repeated, rounded or stretched",
            "answer": "border-image-repeat"
          },
          {
            "position": 6,
            "question": "Specifies how to slice the border image",
            "answer": "border-image-slice"
          },
          {
            "position": 7,
            "question": "A shorthand property for the four border-*-radius properties",
            "answer": "border-radius"
          },
          {
            "position": 8,
            "question": "Sets the style of the left border",
            "answer": "border-left-style"
          },
          {
            "position": 9,
            "question": "Specifies the column width",
            "answer": "column-width"
          },
          {
            "position": 10,
            "question": "A shorthand property for column-width and column-count",
            "answer": "columns"
          },
          {
            "position": 11,
            "question": "Sets the distance between the borders of adjacent cells",
            "answer": "border-spacing"
          },
          {
            "position": 12,
            "question": "Sets the elements position, from the bottom of its parent element",
            "answer": "bottom"
          },
          {
            "position": 13,
            "question": "Specifies the initial length of a flexible item",
            "answer": "flex-basis"
          },
          {
            "position": 14,
            "question": "Specifies how much the item will grow relative to the rest",
            "answer": "flex-grow"
          },
          {
            "position": 15,
            "question": "Specifies how the item will shrink relative to the rest",
            "answer": "flex-shrink"
          },
          {
            "position": 16,
            "question": "Specifies whether the flexible items should wrap or not",
            "answer": "flex-wrap"
          },
          {
            "position": 17,
            "question": "A shorthand property for the grid-column-start and the grid-column-end properties",
            "answer": "grid-column"
          },
          {
            "position": 18,
            "question": "Specifies the size of the gap between columns",
            "answer": "grid-column-gap"
          },
          {
            "position": 19,
            "question": "Specifies where to start the grid item",
            "answer": "grid-column-start"
          },
          {
            "position": 20,
            "question": "A shorthand property for the grid-row-gap and grid-column-gap properties",
            "answer": "grid-gap"
          },
          {
            "position": 21,
            "question": "A shorthand property for the grid-row-start and the grid-row-end properties",
            "answer": "grid-row"
          },
          {
            "position": 22,
            "question": "Specifies where to end the grid item",
            "answer": "grid-row-end"
          },
          {
            "position": 23,
            "question": "Specifies the size of the gap between rows",
            "answer": "grid-row-gap"
          },
          {
            "position": 24,
            "question": "Specifies where to start the grid item",
            "answer": "grid-row-start"
          },
          {
            "position": 25,
            "question": "Specifies the size of the columns, and how many columns in a grid layout",
            "answer": "grid-template-columns"
          },
          {
            "position": 26,
            "question": "Specifies the size of the rows in a grid layout",
            "answer": "grid-template-rows"
          },
          {
            "position": 27,
            "question": "Specifies the size of an element in the inline direction",
            "answer": "inline-size"
          },
          {
            "position": 28,
            "question": "Sets how to split words to improve the layout of paragraphs",
            "answer": "hyphens"
          },
          {
            "position": 29,
            "question": "Specifies the alignment between the items inside a flexible container when the items do not use all available space",
            "answer": "justify-content"
          },
          {
            "position": 30,
            "question": "Increases or decreases the space between characters in a text",
            "answer": "letter-spacing"
          },
          {
            "position": 31,
            "question": "Is set on the grid container. Specifies the alignment of grid items in the inline direction",
            "answer": "justify-items"
          },
          {
            "position": 32,
            "question": "Is set on the grid item. Specifies the alignment of the grid item in the inline direction",
            "answer": "justify-self"
          },
          {
            "position": 33,
            "question": "Sets all the properties for a list in one declaration",
            "answer": "list-style"
          },
          {
            "position": 34,
            "question": "Specifies an image as the list-item marker",
            "answer": "list-style-image"
          },
          {
            "position": 35,
            "question": "Specifies the position of the list-item markers (bullet points)",
            "answer": "list-style-position"
          },
          {
            "position": 36,
            "question": "Specifies the type of list-item marker",
            "answer": "list-style-type"
          },
          {
            "position": 37,
            "question": "Specifies the margin in the inline direction",
            "answer": "margin-inline"
          },
          {
            "position": 38,
            "question": "Specifies the margin at the end in the inline direction",
            "answer": "margin-inline-end"
          },
          {
            "position": 39,
            "question": "Sets the order of the flexible item, relative to the rest",
            "answer": "order"
          },
          {
            "position": 40,
            "question": "Specifies the margin at the start in the inline direction",
            "answer": "margin-inline-start"
          },
          {
            "position": 41,
            "question": "Sets the maximum size of an element in the block direction",
            "answer": "max-block-size"
          },
          {
            "position": 42,
            "question": "Sets the maximum size of an element in the inline direction",
            "answer": "max-inline-size"
          },
          {
            "position": 43,
            "question": "Sets the minimum size of an element in the block direction",
            "answer": "min-block-size"
          },
          {
            "position": 44,
            "question": "Sets the minimum size of an element in the inline direction",
            "answer": "min-inline-size"
          },
          {
            "position": 45,
            "question": "Specifies how the mask layer image is repeated",
            "answer": "mask-repeat"
          },
          {
            "position": 46,
            "question": "Specifies the size of a mask layer image",
            "answer": "mask-size"
          },
          {
            "position": 47,
            "question": "A shorthand property for the row-gap and the column-gap properties",
            "answer": "gap"
          },
          {
            "position": 48,
            "question": "Attaches one or more shadows to an element",
            "answer": "box-shadow"
          },
          {
            "position": 49,
            "question": "Specifies where to end the grid item",
            "answer": "grid-column-end"
          },
          {
            "position": 50,
            "question": "Defines how the width and height of an element are calculated: should they include padding and borders, or not",
            "answer": "box-sizing"
          },
          {
            "position": 51,
            "question": "Specifies the mouse cursor to be displayed when pointing over an element",
            "answer": "cursor"
          },
          {
            "position": 52,
            "question": "Specifies the text direction/writing direction",
            "answer": "direction"
          },
          {
            "position": 53,
            "question": "Specifies how a certain HTML element should be displayed",
            "answer": "display"
          },
          {
            "position": 54,
            "question": "Offsets an outline, and draws it beyond the border edge",
            "answer": "outline-offset"
          },
          {
            "position": 55,
            "question": "Specifies the padding at the end in the block direction",
            "answer": "padding-block-end"
          },
          {
            "position": 56,
            "question": "Specifies the padding at the start in the block direction",
            "answer": "padding-block-start"
          },
          {
            "position": 57,
            "question": "Specifies the padding at the end in the inline direction",
            "answer": "padding-inline-end"
          },
          {
            "position": 58,
            "question": "Specifies the padding at the start in the inline direction",
            "answer": "padding-inline-start"
          },
          {
            "position": 59,
            "question": "Sets the page-break behavior after an element",
            "answer": "page-break-after"
          },
          {
            "position": 60,
            "question": "Sets the page-break behavior before an element",
            "answer": "page-break-before"
          },
          {
            "position": 61,
            "question": "Sets the page-break behavior inside an element",
            "answer": "page-break-inside"
          },
          {
            "position": 62,
            "question": "Specifies the type of positioning method used for an element (static, relative, absolute or fixed)",
            "answer": "position"
          },
          {
            "position": 63,
            "question": "Defines whether or not an element reacts to pointer events",
            "answer": "pointer-events"
          },
          {
            "position": 64,
            "question": "Specifies the rotation of an element",
            "answer": "rotate"
          },
          {
            "position": 65,
            "question": "Specifies the gap between the grid rows",
            "answer": "row-gap"
          },
          {
            "position": 66,
            "question": "Sets the type of quotation marks for embedded quotations",
            "answer": "quotes"
          },
          {
            "position": 67,
            "question": "Specifies the width of a tab character",
            "answer": "tab-size"
          },
          {
            "position": 68,
            "question": "Defines the algorithm used to lay out table cells, rows, and columns",
            "answer": "table-layout"
          },
          {
            "position": 69,
            "question": "Specifies the justification method used when text-align is 'justify'",
            "answer": "text-justify"
          },
          {
            "position": 70,
            "question": "Defines the orientation of characters in a line",
            "answer": "text-orientation"
          },
          {
            "position": 71,
            "question": "Adds shadow to text",
            "answer": "text-shadow"
          },
          {
            "position": 72,
            "question": "Specifies the top position of a positioned element",
            "answer": "top"
          },
          {
            "position": 73,
            "question": "A shorthand property for all the transition-* properties",
            "answer": "transition"
          },
          {
            "position": 74,
            "question": "Specifies whether or not an element is visible",
            "answer": "visibility"
          },
          {
            "position": 75,
            "question": "Specifies how white-space inside an element is handled",
            "answer": "white-space"
          },
          {
            "position": 76,
            "question": "Specifies a delay for the start of an animation",
            "answer": "animation-delay"
          },
          {
            "position": 77,
            "question": "Specifies whether the animation is running or paused",
            "answer": "animation-play-state"
          },
          {
            "position": 78,
            "question": "Specifies an accent color for user-interface controls",
            "answer": "accent-color"
          },
          {
            "position": 79,
            "question": "A shorthand property for all the column-rule-* properties",
            "answer": "column-rule"
          },
          {
            "position": 80,
            "question": "Specifies how to fill columns, balanced or not",
            "answer": "column-fill"
          },
          {
            "position": 81,
            "question": "Specifies the number of columns an element should be divided into",
            "answer": "column-count"
          },
          {
            "position": 82,
            "question": "Specifies what happens if content overflows an element's box",
            "answer": "overflow"
          },
          {
            "position": 83,
            "question": "Specifies how words should break when reaching the end of a line",
            "answer": "word-break"
          },
          {
            "position": 84,
            "question": "Increases or decreases the space between words in a text",
            "answer": "word-spacing"
          },
          {
            "position": 85,
            "question": "Allows long, unbreakable words to be broken and wrap to the next line",
            "answer": "word-wrap"
          },
          {
            "position": 86,
            "question": "Sets the stack order of a positioned element",
            "answer": "z-index"
          },
          {
            "position": 87,
            "question": "Sets the style of an outline",
            "answer": "outline-style"
          },
          {
            "position": 88,
            "question": "Specifies whether to smoothly animate the scroll position in a scrollable box, instead of a straight jump",
            "answer": "scroll-behavior"
          },
          {
            "position": 89,
            "question": "Defines if (and how) an element is resizable by the user",
            "answer": "resize"
          },
          {
            "position": 90,
            "question": "Describes how the last line of a block or a line right before a forced line break is aligned when text-align is 'justify'",
            "answer": "text-align-last"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "four": [
          {
            "position": 0,
            "question": "Specifies the name of the CSS property the transition effect is for",
            "answer": "transition-property"
          },
          {
            "position": 1,
            "question": "Specifies the position of an element",
            "answer": "translate"
          },
          {
            "position": 2,
            "question": "Specifies whether the text of an element can be selected",
            "answer": "user-select"
          },
          {
            "position": 3,
            "question": "Specifies how auto-placed items are inserted in the grid",
            "answer": "grid-auto-flow"
          },
          {
            "position": 4,
            "question": "Defines how far the background (color or image) should extend within an element",
            "answer": "background-clip"
          },
          {
            "position": 5,
            "question": "Applies a 2D or 3D transformation to an element",
            "answer": "transform"
          },
          {
            "position": 6,
            "question": "Specifies a default row size",
            "answer": "grid-auto-rows"
          },
          {
            "position": 7,
            "question": "Specifies whether or not a text should be displayed in a small-caps font",
            "answer": "font-variant"
          },
          {
            "position": 8,
            "question": "Specifies a default column size",
            "answer": "grid-auto-columns"
          },
          {
            "position": 9,
            "question": "Specifies the combination of multiple characters into the space of a single character",
            "answer": "text-combine-upright"
          },
          {
            "position": 10,
            "question": "Allows you to change the position on transformed elements",
            "answer": "transform-origin"
          },
          {
            "position": 11,
            "question": "Specifies how many seconds or milliseconds a transition effect takes to complete",
            "answer": "transition-duration"
          },
          {
            "position": 12,
            "question": "Specifies the distance between an element and the parent element in the inline direction",
            "answer": "inset-inline"
          },
          {
            "position": 13,
            "question": "Selects a normal, condensed, or expanded face from a font family",
            "answer": "font-stretch"
          },
          {
            "position": 14,
            "question": "Specifies when the transition effect will start",
            "answer": "transition-delay"
          },
          {
            "position": 15,
            "question": "Specifies the distance between the start of an element and the parent element in the inline direction",
            "answer": "inset-inline-start"
          },
          {
            "position": 16,
            "question": "Specifies the distance between the end of an element and the parent element in the inline direction",
            "answer": "inset-inline-end"
          },
          {
            "position": 17,
            "question": "Specifies the distance between the start of an element and the parent element in the block direction",
            "answer": "inset-block-start"
          },
          {
            "position": 18,
            "question": "Specifies the type of algorithm to use for image scaling",
            "answer": "image-rendering"
          },
          {
            "position": 19,
            "question": "Specifies the distance between an element and the parent element",
            "answer": "inset"
          },
          {
            "position": 20,
            "question": "Specifies a name for the keyframes animation",
            "answer": "animation-name"
          },
          {
            "position": 21,
            "question": "Increases or decreases the value of one or more CSS counters",
            "answer": "counter-increment"
          },
          {
            "position": 22,
            "question": "Specifies the distance between the end of an element and the parent element in the block direction",
            "answer": "inset-block-end"
          },
          {
            "position": 23,
            "question": "A shorthand property for the flex-direction and the flex-wrap properties",
            "answer": "flex-flow"
          },
          {
            "position": 24,
            "question": "Creates or resets one or more CSS counters",
            "answer": "counter-reset"
          },
          {
            "position": 25,
            "question": "Defines a graphical effect to the area behind an element",
            "answer": "backdrop-filter"
          },
          {
            "position": 26,
            "question": "Specifies how many columns an element should span across",
            "answer": "column-span"
          },
          {
            "position": 27,
            "question": "Specifies whether or not to display borders and background on empty cells in a table",
            "answer": "empty-cells"
          },
          {
            "position": 28,
            "question": "Clips an absolutely positioned element",
            "answer": "clip"
          },
          {
            "position": 29,
            "question": "Defines whether or not the back face of an element should be visible when facing the user",
            "answer": "backface-visibility"
          },
          {
            "position": 30,
            "question": "Specifies the distance between an element and the parent element in the block direction",
            "answer": "inset-block"
          },
          {
            "position": 31,
            "question": "A rule that allows websites to download and use fonts other than the 'web-safe' fonts",
            "answer": "font-face"
          },
          {
            "position": 32,
            "question": "Specifies the width of the rule between columns",
            "answer": "column-rule-width"
          },
          {
            "position": 33,
            "question": "Specifies whether to have scroll chaining or overscroll affordance in x- and y-directions",
            "answer": "overscroll-behavior"
          },
          {
            "position": 34,
            "question": "Specifies the style of the rule between columns",
            "answer": "column-rule-style"
          },
          {
            "position": 35,
            "question": "Specifies the color of the rule between columns",
            "answer": "column-rule-color"
          },
          {
            "position": 36,
            "question": "Specifies whether or not to clip the top/bottom edges of the content, if it overflows the element's content area",
            "answer": "overflow-y"
          },
          {
            "position": 37,
            "question": "Specifies whether to have scroll chaining or overscroll affordance in the block direction",
            "answer": "overscroll-behavior-block"
          },
          {
            "position": 38,
            "question": "Specifies whether or not to clip the left/right edges of the content, if it overflows the element's content area",
            "answer": "overflow-x"
          },
          {
            "position": 39,
            "question": "Specifies whether to have scroll chaining or overscroll affordance in the inline direction",
            "answer": "overscroll-behavior-inline"
          },
          {
            "position": 40,
            "question": "Specifies whether to have scroll chaining or overscroll affordance in y-directions",
            "answer": "overscroll-behavior-y"
          },
          {
            "position": 41,
            "question": "Specifies rotation of an element as it is animated along a path",
            "answer": "offset-rotate"
          },
          {
            "position": 42,
            "question": "Specifies the distance from the top of the container to the snap position on the child elements",
            "answer": "scroll-padding-top"
          },
          {
            "position": 43,
            "question": "Specifies whether to have scroll chaining or overscroll affordance in x-direction",
            "answer": "overscroll-behavior-x"
          },
          {
            "position": 44,
            "question": "Specifies what should happen with the element that is next to a floating element",
            "answer": "clear"
          },
          {
            "position": 45,
            "question": "Specifies whether or not the browser can break lines with long words, if they overflow the container",
            "answer": "overflow-wrap"
          },
          {
            "position": 46,
            "question": "Specifies the path an element is animated along",
            "answer": "offset-path"
          },
          {
            "position": 47,
            "question": "Specifies the distance from the right side of the container to the snap position on the child elements",
            "answer": "scroll-padding-right"
          },
          {
            "position": 48,
            "question": "Specifies the distance from the left side of the container to the snap position on the child elements",
            "answer": "scroll-padding-left"
          },
          {
            "position": 49,
            "question": "Specifies the distance in inline direction from the start of the container to the snap position on the child elements",
            "answer": "scroll-padding-inline-start"
          },
          {
            "position": 50,
            "question": "Specifies the distance in inline direction from the end of the container to the snap position on the child elements",
            "answer": "scroll-padding-inline-end"
          },
          {
            "position": 51,
            "question": "Specifies the distance in inline direction from the container to the snap position on the child elements",
            "answer": "scroll-padding-inline"
          },
          {
            "position": 52,
            "question": "Specifies the distance from the bottom of the container to the snap position on the child elements",
            "answer": "scroll-padding-bottom"
          },
          {
            "position": 53,
            "question": "Specifies the distance in block direction from the start of the container to the snap position on the child elements",
            "answer": "scroll-padding-block-start"
          },
          {
            "position": 54,
            "question": "Specifies the distance in block direction from the end of the container to the snap position on the child elements",
            "answer": "scroll-padding-block-end"
          },
          {
            "position": 55,
            "question": "Specifies the distance in block direction from the container to the snap position on the child elements",
            "answer": "scroll-padding-block"
          },
          {
            "position": 56,
            "question": "Specifies the distance from the container to the snap position on the child elements",
            "answer": "scroll-padding"
          },
          {
            "position": 57,
            "question": "Specifies the margin between the snap position on the top side and the container",
            "answer": "scroll-margin-top"
          },
          {
            "position": 58,
            "question": "Specifies the margin between the snap position on the right side and the container",
            "answer": "scroll-margin-right"
          },
          {
            "position": 59,
            "question": "Specifies the margin between the snap position on the left side and the container",
            "answer": "scroll-margin-left"
          },
          {
            "position": 60,
            "question": "Specifies the start margin between the snap position and the container in the inline direction",
            "answer": "scroll-margin-inline-start"
          },
          {
            "position": 61,
            "question": "Specifies the end margin between the snap position and the container in the inline direction",
            "answer": "scroll-margin-inline-end"
          },
          {
            "position": 62,
            "question": "Specifies the margin between the snap position and the container in the inline direction",
            "answer": "scroll-margin-inline"
          },
          {
            "position": 63,
            "question": "Specifies the margin between the snap position on the bottom side and the container",
            "answer": "scroll-margin-bottom"
          },
          {
            "position": 64,
            "question": "Specifies the end margin between the snap position and the container in the block direction",
            "answer": "scroll-margin-block-end"
          },
          {
            "position": 65,
            "question": "Specifies the margin between the snap position and the container in the block direction",
            "answer": "scroll-margin-block"
          },
          {
            "position": 66,
            "question": "Specifies the margin between the snap position and the container",
            "answer": "scroll-margin"
          },
          {
            "position": 67,
            "question": "Specifies align-self and justify-self property values for grid layouts",
            "answer": "place-self"
          },
          {
            "position": 68,
            "question": "Specifies the start margin between the snap position and the container in the block direction",
            "answer": "scroll-margin-block-start"
          },
          {
            "position": 69,
            "question": "Specifies the size of an element by scaling up or down",
            "answer": "scale"
          },
          {
            "position": 70,
            "question": "Specifies align-items and justify-items property values for grid layouts",
            "answer": "place-items"
          },
          {
            "position": 71,
            "question": "Defines at which position the user is looking at the 3D-positioned element",
            "answer": "perspective-origin"
          },
          {
            "position": 72,
            "question": "Gives a 3D-positioned element some perspective",
            "answer": "perspective"
          },
          {
            "position": 73,
            "question": "Specifies align-content and justify-content property values for flexbox and grid layouts",
            "answer": "place-content"
          },
          {
            "position": 74,
            "question": "Sets the order of how an SVG element or text is painted.",
            "answer": "paint-order"
          },
          {
            "position": 75,
            "question": "Specifies an image to be used as a mask layer for an element",
            "answer": "mask-image"
          },
          {
            "position": 76,
            "question": "Specifies whether or not content in viewable area in a scrollable contianer should be pushed down when new content is loaded above",
            "answer": "overflow-anchor"
          },
          {
            "position": 77,
            "question": "Specifies how an element's content should blend with its direct parent background",
            "answer": "mix-blend-mode"
          },
          {
            "position": 78,
            "question": "Sets the starting position of a mask layer image (relative to the mask position area)",
            "answer": "mask-position"
          },
          {
            "position": 79,
            "question": "Specifies the origin position (the mask position area) of a mask layer image",
            "answer": "mask-origin"
          },
          {
            "position": 80,
            "question": "Represents a compositing operation used on the current mask layer with the mask layers below it",
            "answer": "mask-composite"
          },
          {
            "position": 81,
            "question": "Specifies the mask area",
            "answer": "mask-clip"
          },
          {
            "position": 82,
            "question": "Hides parts of an element by masking or clipping an image at specific places",
            "answer": "mask"
          },
          {
            "position": 83,
            "question": "Specifies the color of the cursor (caret) in inputs, textareas, or any element that is editable",
            "answer": "caret-color"
          },
          {
            "position": 84,
            "question": "Defines the radius of the border of the top-right corner",
            "answer": "border-top-right-radius"
          },
          {
            "position": 85,
            "question": "The BLANK property is used to create a reflection of an element",
            "answer": "box-reflect"
          },
          {
            "position": 86,
            "question": "Defines the radius of the border of the top-left corner",
            "answer": "border-top-left-radius"
          },
          {
            "position": 87,
            "question": "Specifies how long an animation should take to complete one cycle",
            "answer": "animation-duration"
          },
          {
            "position": 88,
            "question": "Specifies the path to the image to be used as a border",
            "answer": "border-image-source"
          },
          {
            "position": 89,
            "question": "Sets the width of the borders at start and end in the inline direction",
            "answer": "border-inline-width"
          },
          {
            "position": 90,
            "question": "Sets the style of the borders at start and end in the inline direction",
            "answer": "border-inline-style"
          },
          {
            "position": 91,
            "question": "Sets the width of the border at the start in the inline direction",
            "answer": "border-inline-start-width"
          },
          {
            "position": 92,
            "question": "Sets the color of the border at the start in the inline direction",
            "answer": "border-inline-start-color"
          },
          {
            "position": 93,
            "question": "Defines the radius of the border of the bottom-right corner",
            "answer": "border-bottom-right-radius"
          },
          {
            "position": 94,
            "question": "Sets the style of the border at the start in the inline direction",
            "answer": "border-inline-start-style"
          },
          {
            "position": 95,
            "question": "Sets the style of the borders at start and end in the block direction",
            "answer": "border-block-style"
          },
          {
            "position": 96,
            "question": "Specifies the amount by which the border image area extends beyond the border box",
            "answer": "border-image-outset"
          },
          {
            "position": 97,
            "question": "Sets the color of the border at the end in the inline direction",
            "answer": "border-inline-end-color"
          },
          {
            "position": 98,
            "question": "Sets the width of the border at the end in the inline direction",
            "answer": "border-inline-end-width"
          },
          {
            "position": 99,
            "question": "Defines the radius of the border of the bottom-left corner",
            "answer": "border-bottom-left-radius"
          },
          {
            "position": 100,
            "question": "Sets the width of the borders at start and end in the block direction",
            "answer": "border-block-width"
          },
          {
            "position": 101,
            "question": "Sets the width of the border at the start in the block direction",
            "answer": "border-block-start-width"
          },
          {
            "position": 102,
            "question": "Sets the style of the border at the start in the block direction",
            "answer": "border-block-start-style"
          },
          {
            "position": 103,
            "question": "Sets the color of the border at the start in the block direction",
            "answer": "border-block-start-color"
          },
          {
            "position": 104,
            "question": "Sets the width of the border at the end in the block direction",
            "answer": "border-block-end-width"
          },
          {
            "position": 105,
            "question": "Sets the style of the border at the end in the block direction",
            "answer": "border-block-end-style"
          },
          {
            "position": 106,
            "question": "Sets the color of the border at the end in the block direction",
            "answer": "border-block-end-color"
          },
          {
            "position": 107,
            "question": "Sets the color of the borders at start and end in the block direction",
            "answer": "border-block-color"
          },
          {
            "position": 108,
            "question": "Specifies whether an animation should be played forwards, backwards or in alternate cycles",
            "answer": "animation-direction"
          },
          {
            "position": 109,
            "question": "Resets all properties (except unicode-bidi and direction)",
            "answer": "all"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "five": [
          {
            "position": 0,
            "question": "Specifies how nested elements are rendered in 3D space",
            "answer": "transform-style"
          },
          {
            "position": 1,
            "question": "Specifies the speed curve of the transition effect",
            "answer": "transition-timing-function"
          },
          {
            "position": 2,
            "question": "Used together with the direction property to set or return whether the text should be overridden to support multiple languages in the same document",
            "answer": "unicode-bidi"
          },
          {
            "position": 3,
            "question": "Sets the minimum number of lines that must be left at the top of a page or column",
            "answer": "widows"
          },
          {
            "position": 4,
            "question": "Specifies the position along a path where an animated element is placed",
            "answer": "offset-distance"
          },
          {
            "position": 5,
            "question": "Sets the minimum number of lines that must be left at the bottom of a page or column",
            "answer": "orphans"
          },
          {
            "position": 6,
            "question": "Specifies where to position elements when the user stops scrolling",
            "answer": "scroll-snap-align"
          },
          {
            "position": 7,
            "question": "Specifies a point on an element that is fixed to the path it is animated along",
            "answer": "offset-anchor"
          },
          {
            "position": 8,
            "question": "Specifies scroll behaviour after fast swipe on trackpad or touch screen",
            "answer": "scroll-snap-stop"
          },
          {
            "position": 9,
            "question": "Specifies whether lines of text are laid out horizontally or vertically",
            "answer": "writing-mode"
          },
          {
            "position": 10,
            "question": "Is a shorthand, and specifies how to animate an element along a path",
            "answer": "offset"
          },
          {
            "position": 11,
            "question": "Specifies the alignment of the replaced element inside its box",
            "answer": "object-position"
          },
          {
            "position": 12,
            "question": "Specifies whether the mask layer image is treated as a luminance mask or as an alpha mask",
            "answer": "mask-mode"
          },
          {
            "position": 13,
            "question": "Specifies whether an SVG <mask> element is treated as a luminance mask or as an alpha mask",
            "answer": "mask-type"
          },
          {
            "position": 14,
            "question": "Defines effects (e.g. blurring or color shifting) on an element before the element is displayed",
            "answer": "filter"
          },
          {
            "position": 15,
            "question": "Defines whether an element must create a new stacking content",
            "answer": "isolation"
          },
          {
            "position": 16,
            "question": "Specifies whether a punctuation character may be placed outside the line box",
            "answer": "hanging-punctuation"
          },
          {
            "position": 17,
            "question": "Specifies the animation code",
            "answer": "keyframes"
          },
          {
            "position": 18,
            "question": "Specifies how the contents of a replaced element should be fitted to the box established by its used height and width",
            "answer": "object-fit"
          },
          {
            "position": 19,
            "question": "Controls the usage of alternate glyphs of smaller size positioned as superscript or subscript regarding the baseline of the font",
            "answer": "font-variant-position"
          },
          {
            "position": 20,
            "question": "Used with the :before and :after pseudo-elements, to insert generated content",
            "answer": "content"
          },
          {
            "position": 21,
            "question": "Either specifies a name for the grid item, or this property is a shorthand property for the grid-row-start, grid-column-start, grid-row-end, and grid-column-end properties",
            "answer": "grid-area"
          },
          {
            "position": 22,
            "question": "Controls the usage of alternate glyphs for numbers, fractions, and ordinal markers",
            "answer": "font-variant-numeric"
          },
          {
            "position": 23,
            "question": "Controls the usage of alternate glyphs for East Asian scripts (e.g Japanese and Chinese)",
            "answer": "font-variant-east-asian"
          },
          {
            "position": 24,
            "question": "Controls which ligatures and contextual forms are used in textual content of the elements it applies to",
            "answer": "font-variant-ligatures"
          },
          {
            "position": 25,
            "question": "Controls the usage of alternate glyphs for capital letters",
            "answer": "font-variant-caps"
          },
          {
            "position": 26,
            "question": "Controls the usage of alternate glyphs associated to alternative names defined in font-feature-values",
            "answer": "font-variant-alternates"
          },
          {
            "position": 27,
            "question": "Controls which missing typefaces (bold or italic) may be synthesized by the browser",
            "answer": "font-synthesis"
          },
          {
            "position": 28,
            "question": "Preserves the readability of text when font fallback occurs",
            "answer": "font-size-adjust"
          },
          {
            "position": 29,
            "question": "Controls the usage of language-specific glyphs in a typeface",
            "answer": "font-language-override"
          },
          {
            "position": 30,
            "question": "Controls the usage of the kerning information (how letters are spaced)",
            "answer": "font-kerning"
          },
          {
            "position": 31,
            "question": "Allows authors to use a common name in font-variant-alternate for feature activated differently in OpenType",
            "answer": "font-feature-values"
          },
          {
            "position": 32,
            "question": "Allows control over advanced typographic features in OpenType fonts",
            "answer": "font-feature-settings"
          },
          {
            "position": 33,
            "question": "Specifies the character encoding used in the style sheet",
            "answer": "charset"
          },
          {
            "position": 34,
            "question": "Specifies the placement of a table caption",
            "answer": "caption-side"
          },
          {
            "position": 35,
            "question": "Specifies whether or not a page-, column-, or region-break should occur inside the specified element",
            "answer": "break-inside"
          },
          {
            "position": 36,
            "question": "Specifies whether or not a page-, column-, or region-break should occur before the specified element",
            "answer": "break-before"
          },
          {
            "position": 37,
            "question": "Specifies whether or not a page-, column-, or region-break should occur after the specified element",
            "answer": "break-after"
          },
          {
            "position": 38,
            "question": "Sets the behavior of the background and border of an element at page-break, or, for in-line elements, at line-break.",
            "answer": "box-decoration-break"
          },
          {
            "position": 39,
            "question": "Sets the style of the border at the end in the inline direction",
            "answer": "border-inline-end-style"
          },
          {
            "position": 40,
            "question": "Specifies the speed curve of an animation",
            "answer": "animation-timing-function"
          },
          {
            "position": 41,
            "question": "Specifies the number of times an animation should be played",
            "answer": "animation-iteration-count"
          },
          {
            "position": 42,
            "question": "Specifies a style for the element when the animation is not playing (before it starts, after it ends, or both)",
            "answer": "animation-fill-mode"
          },
          {
            "position": 43,
            "question": "Specifies how snap behaviour should be when scrolling",
            "answer": "scroll-snap-type"
          }
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  "html_basics": {
    "level": [
      {
        "one": [
          {
            "position": 0,
            "question": "The HTML <BLANK> Element represents the content of an HTML document. There can be only one <BLANK> element in a document.",
            "answer": "body"
          },
          {
            "position": 1,
            "question": "The <BLANK> tag represents a paragraph. HTML paragraphs can be any structural grouping of related content, such as images or form fields.",
            "answer": "p"
          },
          {
            "position": 2,
            "question": "The <BLANK> tag is a block element. It defines a division or a section in HTML document. Any sort of content can be put inside the <BLANK> tag.",
            "answer": "div"
          },
          {
            "position": 3,
            "question": "The HTML <BLANK> element is used to represent an item in a list.",
            "answer": "li"
          },
          {
            "position": 4,
            "question": "The BLANK tag contains the width attribute. As the name suggests, these attributes specify the width of the image in pixels).",
            "answer": "width"
          },
          {
            "position": 5,
            "question": "The BLANK tag contains the height attribute. As the name suggests, these attributes specify the height of the image in pixels).",
            "answer": "height"
          },
          {
            "position": 6,
            "question": "The HTML <BLANK> tag is used to link images to web pages.",
            "answer": "img"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "two": [
          {
            "position": 0,
            "question": "<BLANK> This is the Smallest among all. </BLANK>",
            "answer": "h6"
          },
          {
            "position": 1,
            "question": "<BLANK> This is the second smallest heading of all. </BLANK>",
            "answer": "h5"
          },
          {
            "position": 2,
            "question": "<BLANK> This is the fourth largest heading among all. </BLANK>",
            "answer": "h4"
          },
          {
            "position": 3,
            "question": "<BLANK> This is the third largest heading among all. </BLANK>",
            "answer": "h3"
          },
          {
            "position": 4,
            "question": "<BLANK> This is the second largest heading among all. </BLANK>",
            "answer": "h2"
          },
          {
            "position": 5,
            "question": "The <BLANK> HTML element defines the documents title that is shown in a browsers title bar or a pages tab.",
            "answer": "title"
          },
          {
            "position": 6,
            "question": "The <BLANK> tag is used to define style information (CSS) for a document. It is used to specify how HTML elements should render in a browser.",
            "answer": "style"
          },
          {
            "position": 7,
            "question": "The <BLANK> HTML5 element is used to give introductory content about the document. It may contain some heading elements and also a logo, a search form, an author name, and other elements.",
            "answer": "header"
          },
          {
            "position": 8,
            "question": "The <BLANK> HTML element represents the main dominant content of the <body> of a document. The main content area consists of content that expands upon the central topic of a document, or the main functionality of an application.",
            "answer": "main"
          },
          {
            "position": 9,
            "question": "<BLANK> This is the largest heading among all. </BLANK>",
            "answer": "h1"
          },
          {
            "position": 10,
            "question": "The <BLANK> HTML element represents a footer for its sectioning root element. It typically contains information about the author of the section, copyright data or links to related documents.",
            "answer": "footer"
          },
          {
            "position": 11,
            "question": "The <BLANK> tag is used to make the text enclosed within these tags bold.",
            "answer": "b"
          },
          {
            "position": 12,
            "question": "The <BLANK> tag is used to make the style text enclosed within these tags italics.",
            "answer": "i"
          },
          {
            "position": 13,
            "question": "The HTML <BLANK> element represents an unordered list of items. It is typically rendered as a bulleted list.",
            "answer": "ul"
          },
          {
            "position": 14,
            "question": "The HTML <BLANK> element represents an ordered list of items. It is typically rendered as a numbered list.",
            "answer": "ol"
          },
          {
            "position": 15,
            "question": "The BLANK attribute helps us change the look and feel of the document by setting the style, such as font, size, color, etc. of the HTML element.",
            "answer": "style"
          },
          {
            "position": 16,
            "question": "The BLANK attribute is a unique identifier that is used to specify an area of a webpage. It is used by CSS and JavaScript to perform a certain task for a unique element. In CSS, the BLANK attribute is used using the # symbol followed by BLANK.",
            "answer": "id"
          },
          {
            "position": 17,
            "question": "The BLANK attribute is used to specify one or more class names for an element and assign different properties within one block which in turn can be assigned to any element. Once assigned a specific class, the elements will have all the properties of that particular class.",
            "answer": "class"
          },
          {
            "position": 18,
            "question": "The BLANK attribute is used with the image tag. It helps us to specify the alternative text in case, the image cannot be displayed on the website to give the users an idea of what the image contains.",
            "answer": "alt"
          },
          {
            "position": 19,
            "question": "We use the <a> tag to define a hyperlink. In this tag, the BLANK attribute specifies the url of the destination address. Without BLANK attribute <a> element will not become hyperlink.",
            "answer": "href"
          },
          {
            "position": 20,
            "question": "The HTML BLANK Attribute is used to specify the URL of the image to be used as a submit button. It specifies the image path inside double quotes.",
            "answer": "src"
          },
          {
            "position": 21,
            "question": "The HTML <BLANK> element represents a clickable button, which can be used in forms or anywhere a standard button functionality is needed in a document.",
            "answer": "button"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "three": [
          {
            "position": 0,
            "question": "The <BLANK> tag is used to represent source codes. It is mainly used to display the code snippet into the web browser.",
            "answer": "code"
          },
          {
            "position": 1,
            "question": "The <BLANK> tag is an empty element, it defines the relationship between the current document and an external resource. The <BLANK> tag is most often used to link to external style sheets on your website.",
            "answer": "link"
          },
          {
            "position": 2,
            "question": "The HTML5 <BLANK> element represents a standalone section. It is a structural HTML element used to group together related elements. Each <BLANK> typically includes one or more heading elements and additional elements presenting related content.",
            "answer": "section"
          },
          {
            "position": 3,
            "question": "The <BLANK> HTML element represents a section of a page whose purpose is to provide navigation links, either within the current document or to other documents.",
            "answer": "nav"
          },
          {
            "position": 4,
            "question": "The <BLANK> tag is an inline element. It is used to mark up a part of a text, or a part of a document.",
            "answer": "span"
          },
          {
            "position": 5,
            "question": "The <BLANK> tag is used to indicate that content enclosed within these tags has strong importance or urgency. Typically, browsers render their content in bold.",
            "answer": "strong"
          },
          {
            "position": 6,
            "question": "The <BLANK> element is used to describe the title of a creative work (For ex. a book, a paper, an essay, a poem, a song, a painting etc.)",
            "answer": "cite"
          },
          {
            "position": 7,
            "question": "The HTML <BLANK> element represents data in a two-dimensional table comprised of rows and columns.",
            "answer": "table"
          },
          {
            "position": 8,
            "question": "The HTML <BLANK> element is used to group header content in an HTML table. (used in conjunction with the <tbody> and <tfoot> element)",
            "answer": "thead"
          },
          {
            "position": 9,
            "question": "The HTML <BLANK> element is used to group primary content of an HTML table.",
            "answer": "tbody"
          },
          {
            "position": 10,
            "question": "The HTML <BLANK> element is used to define a cell as header of a group of cells of the HTML table.",
            "answer": "th"
          },
          {
            "position": 11,
            "question": "The HTML <BLANK> element defines a cell of a table that contains the main data of the table.",
            "answer": "td"
          },
          {
            "position": 12,
            "question": "The HTML <BLANK> tag defines a row in an HTML table. A <BLANK> element contains one or more <th> or <td> elements",
            "answer": "tr"
          },
          {
            "position": 13,
            "question": "The <BLANK> HTML element represents a document section containing interactive controls for submitting information.",
            "answer": "form"
          },
          {
            "position": 14,
            "question": "The HTML <BLANK> element is used to create interactive controls for web-based forms in order to accept data from the user.",
            "answer": "input"
          },
          {
            "position": 15,
            "question": "The HTML <BLANK> element represents a control that provides a menu of options to select from.",
            "answer": "select"
          },
          {
            "position": 16,
            "question": "The BLANK attribute specifies a short hint that describes the expected value of an input field/text area .The short hint is displayed in the field before the user enters a value.",
            "answer": "placeholder"
          },
          {
            "position": 17,
            "question": "The HTML <BLANK> element displays an indicator showing the degree of completion of a task, typically displayed in the form of a progress bar.",
            "answer": "progress"
          },
          {
            "position": 18,
            "question": "The <BLANK> tag is used to specify a label or caption for an <input> element of a form.",
            "answer": "label"
          },
          {
            "position": 19,
            "question": "The HTML <BLANK> element is used to include sound content in documents. It may contain one or more audio sources.",
            "answer": "audio"
          },
          {
            "position": 20,
            "question": "The HTML <BLANK> element embeds a media player which supports video files into the document.",
            "answer": "video"
          },
          {
            "position": 21,
            "question": "The HTML <BLANK> tag helps embed multimedia in a Web page and play it while opening the page. It uses the three mandatory attributes, namely src, height, and width.",
            "answer": "embed"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "four": [
          {
            "position": 0,
            "question": "The <BLANK> element is a container for metadata which is data about data. It is the first section in the code containing information about a web pages properties and links to external related files.",
            "answer": "head"
          },
          {
            "position": 1,
            "question": "The BLANK tags are tags that have some data such as text, the image between their opening and closing tags. There are several BLANK tags in HTML.",
            "answer": "container"
          },
          {
            "position": 2,
            "question": "The HTML5 <BLANK> element represents a self-contained composition in a document, page, application, or site, which is independently distributable or reusable.",
            "answer": "article"
          },
          {
            "position": 3,
            "question": "The <BLANK> tag is used to put stress on some text or show some degree of emphasis. The <BLANK> element can be nested as well, where each level of nesting indicates a greater degree of emphasis.",
            "answer": "em"
          },
          {
            "position": 4,
            "question": "The <BLANK> element is used to represent an abbreviation or acronym. The optional title attribute can be used to add description of the abbreviation.",
            "answer": "abbr"
          },
          {
            "position": 5,
            "question": "The <BLANK> tag is used to mark or highlight important text for reference or notation purposes.",
            "answer": "mark"
          },
          {
            "position": 6,
            "question": "The <BLANK> element is used to represent a specific period of time.",
            "answer": "time"
          },
          {
            "position": 7,
            "question": "The HTML <BLANK> element represents a description list. The element encloses a list of groups of terms (specified using the <dt> element) and descriptions.",
            "answer": "dl"
          },
          {
            "position": 8,
            "question": "The <BLANK> element specifies the title or caption of a table.",
            "answer": "caption"
          },
          {
            "position": 9,
            "question": "The BLANK attribute specifies extra information about an element. The text of the BLANK attribute is most often displayed as a tooltip when the mouse hovers over the element in most browsers.",
            "answer": "title"
          },
          {
            "position": 10,
            "question": "The HTML <BLANK> tag is used to include objects, such as images, audios, videos, Java applets, ActiveX controls, Portable Document Format (PDF), and Flash objects, in a Web page.",
            "answer": "object"
          },
          {
            "position": 11,
            "question": "The <BLANK> tag is used to define an option in a select list. The <BLANK> elements go inside a <select>, <optgroup>, or <datalist> elements.",
            "answer": "option"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "five": [
          {
            "position": 0,
            "question": "The <BLANK> tag represents pre-formatted text which is to be presented exactly as written in the HTML file. . It preserves the text spaces, line breaks, tabs, and other formatting characters which are ignored by web browsers.",
            "answer": "pre"
          },
          {
            "position": 1,
            "question": "The <BLANK> tag defines metadata about an HTML document. It is typically used to specify the character set, page description, keywords, author of the document, and viewport settings.",
            "answer": "meta"
          },
          {
            "position": 2,
            "question": "BLANK elements by default define ARIA landmark. These elements are mostly descendant of HTML body element.",
            "answer": "Sectioning Content"
          },
          {
            "position": 3,
            "question": "The <BLANK> tag defines some content aside from the content it is placed in. Its content should be indirectly related to the surrounding content. The <BLANK> content is ,most often placed as a sidebar in a document.",
            "answer": "aside"
          },
          {
            "position": 4,
            "question": "The HTML <BLANK> element indicates that the enclosed HTML provides contact information for a person or people, or for an organization. It must not contain information other than contact information.",
            "answer": "address"
          },
          {
            "position": 5,
            "question": "The <BLANK> tag is used when we need to write the text as subscript.",
            "answer": "sub"
          },
          {
            "position": 6,
            "question": "The <BLANK> tag is used when we need to write the text as superscript.",
            "answer": "sup"
          },
          {
            "position": 7,
            "question": "The HTML <BLANK> tag is used in conjunction with <dl> to describe a term/name in a description list.",
            "answer": "dd"
          },
          {
            "position": 8,
            "question": "The HTML <BLANK> element is used in conjunction with <dl> to specifies a term in a description or definition list.",
            "answer": "dt"
          },
          {
            "position": 9,
            "question": "The HTML <BLANK> element defines a set of rows summarizing the columns of the table as per requirement.",
            "answer": "tfoot"
          },
          {
            "position": 10,
            "question": "The <BLANK> HTML element is used to create a multi-line plain-text editing control, often used in a form, to collect user inputs like comments or reviews.",
            "answer": "textarea"
          },

          {
            "position": 11,
            "question": "The HTML <BLANK> element is used to create a grouping of options within a <select> element.",
            "answer": "optgroup"
          },

          {
            "position": 12,
            "question": "The HTML <BLANK> element is used to give a predefined options for an <input> element. It adds an autocomplete feature to it.",
            "answer": "datalist"
          },

          {
            "position": 13,
            "question": "The HTML <BLANK> tag is used to group or various diagrams, images, illustrations, and code snippets into the document.",
            "answer": "figure"
          },

          {
            "position": 14,
            "question": "The HTML <BLANK> tag is used inside the <figure> tag to provide the caption of the content.",
            "answer": "figcaption"
          }
        ]
      }
    ]
  },
  "react": {
    "level": [
      {
        "one": [
          {
            "position": 0,
            "question": "The BLANK is a built-in React object that is used to contain data or information about the component.",
            "answer": "state"
          },
          {
            "position": 1,
            "question": "BLANKS allow functional components to have access to state and other React features.",
            "answer": "Hooks"
          },
          {
            "position": 2,
            "question": "BLANK is an open-source front-end JavaScript library that is used for building user interfaces, especially for single-page applications. It is used for handling view layer for web and mobile apps.",
            "answer": "React"
          },
          {
            "position": 3,
            "question": "BLANKS are inputs to components. They are single values or objects containing a set of values that are passed to components on creation using a naming convention similar to HTML-tag attributes. They are data passed down from a parent component to a child component.",
            "answer": "Props"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "two": [
          {
            "position": 0,
            "question": "BLANK is a special keyword in React, which stands for properties, and is being used for passing data from one component to another.",
            "answer": "props"
          },
          {
            "position": 1,
            "question": "The React useBLANK() Hook allows us to track state in a function component.",
            "answer": "State"
          },
          {
            "position": 2,
            "question": "Conceptually, a BLANK is like a JavaScript function. They are the building blocks of React. They accept arbitrary inputs (called props) and return React elements describing what should appear on the screen.",
            "answer": "Component"
          },
          {
            "position": 3,
            "question": "If you are rendering your component using JSX, the name of that component has to begin with a BLANK letter otherwise React will throw an error as an unrecognized tag.",
            "answer": "capital"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "three": [
          {
            "position": 0,
            "question": "The useBLANK() Hook allows you to perform side effects in your components. Some examples of side effects are: fetching data, directly updating the DOM, and timers.",
            "answer": "Effect"
          },
          {
            "position": 1,
            "question": "A/An BLANK is a plain object describing what you want to appear on the screen in terms of the DOM nodes or other components. Once a/an BLANK is created, it is never mutated.",
            "answer": "Element"
          },
          {
            "position": 2,
            "question": "BLANKS get passed to the component similar to function parameters whereas state is managed within the component similar to variables declared within a function.",
            "answer": "Props"
          },
          {
            "position": 3,
            "question": "React.BLANK is a useful component for highlighting potential problems in an application. Just like <Fragment>, <BLANK> does not render any extra DOM elements. It activates additional checks and warnings for its descendants. These checks apply for development mode only.",
            "answer": "StrictMode"
          },
          {
            "position": 4,
            "question": "Each component in React has a BLANK which you can monitor and manipulate during its three main phases. The three phases are: Mounting, Updating, and Unmounting.",
            "answer": "lifecycle"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "four": [
          {
            "position": 0,
            "question": "Executed after first rendering and where all AJAX requests, DOM or state updates, and set up event listeners should occur.",
            "answer": "componentDidMount"
          },
          {
            "position": 1,
            "question": "If the behaviour of a component is dependent on the state of the component then it can be termed as BLANK component. These BLANK components are always class components and have a state that gets initialized in the constructor.",
            "answer": "stateful"
          },
          {
            "position": 2,
            "question": "The useBLANK() Hook allows you to persist values between renders.",
            "answer": "Ref"
          },
          {
            "position": 3,
            "question": "If the behaviour of a component is independent of its state then it can be a BLANK component. A functional component is always a BLANK component, but the class component can be BLANK or stateful.",
            "answer": "stateless"
          },
          {
            "position": 4,
            "question": "A BLANK component is a component that renders one of many components.",
            "answer": "switching"
          },
          {
            "position": 5,
            "question": "Mostly BLANK is used to update the DOM in response to prop or state changes. This will not fire if shouldComponentUpdate() returns false.",
            "answer": "componentDidUpdate"
          },
          {
            "position": 6,
            "question": "useBLANK() is a React Hook that lets you read and subscribe to context from your component.",
            "answer": "Context"
          }
        ]
      },
      {
        "five": [
          {
            "position": 0,
            "question": "If the return value is determined by its input values only and is always the same for the particular input values, then it is considered a BLANK function.",
            "answer": "Pure"
          },
          {
            "position": 1,
            "question": "BLANK will be used to cancel any outgoing network requests, or remove all event listeners associated with the component.",
            "answer": "componentWillUnmount"
          },
          {
            "position": 2,
            "question": "BLANK is a recommended way to render children into a DOM node that exists outside the DOM hierarchy of the parent component.",
            "answer": "Portal"
          },
          {
            "position": 3,
            "question": "When a component's props or state change, React decides whether an actual DOM update is necessary by comparing the newly returned element with the previously rendered one. When they are not equal, React will update the DOM. This process is called BLANK.",
            "answer": "reconciliation"
          },
          {
            "position": 4,
            "question": "Executed right before rendered output is committed to the DOM. Any value returned by this will be passed into componentDidUpdate(). This is useful to capture information from the DOM i.e. scroll position.",
            "answer": "getSnapshotBeforeUpdate"
          },
          {
            "position": 5,
            "question": "Determines if the component will be updated or not. By default, it returns true. If you are sure that the component doesn't need to render after the state or props are updated, you can return a false value. It is a great place to improve performance as it allows you to prevent a re-render if component receives a new prop.",
            "answer": "shouldComponentUpdate"
          },
          {
            "position": 6,
            "question": "Invoked right before calling render() and is invoked on every render. This exists for rare use cases where you need a derived state.",
            "answer": "getDerivedStateFromProps"
          },
          {
            "position": 7,
            "question": "BLANKS let you group a list of children without adding extra nodes to the DOM. It's a common pattern in React which is used for a component to return multiple elements.",
            "answer": "Fragments"
          },
          {
            "position": 8,
            "question": "The BLANK object enables you to render components to static markup (typically used on node server). This object is mainly used for server-side rendering (SSR).",
            "answer": "ReactDOMServer"
          },
          {
            "position": 9,
            "question": "A/AN BLANK function doesn't predictably produce the same result given the same inputs when called multiple times, and may cause side-effects.",
            "answer": "Impure"
          }
        ]
      }
    ]
  }
}